<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>d34c4e59-e6f2-4fce-8ea6-e0da265fbf22</id>
  <title>editx</title>
  <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.333169+00:00</updated>
  <link href="https://www.editx.eu" rel="alternate"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="1.0.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10402</id>
    <title>M365 Platform &amp; Security Architect (Devoteam)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.363401+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Laurent  Huygens, Talent Acquisition Manager – Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Machelen (3 Cullinganlaan 1831 Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on 11/08/2025, last change 11/08/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like these keywords, you’ll love this role:&lt;br&gt;#M365 #Entra #Defender #Purview #Intune&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s more fundamental in IT these days than a Digital Workplace that is fully secured and compliant by end users?&lt;br&gt;Develop, design, and build the future with us as a Microsoft 365 Workplace Security Architect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a Workplace Security Architect, you know the solutions that can help in increasing the workplace security maturity. You know what Zero-trust is and how you can use Microsoft technology to protect customers against cyberthreats. You will work with Client’s Business &amp;amp; Technical employees to capture, discuss, create, build, deliver &amp;amp; verify solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this position, we’re looking for &lt;strong&gt;all seniority levels&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have a broad view of the Modern Workplace building blocks, from classic solutions to Microsoft 365.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have a broad view of all the Microsoft 365 Defender Solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have expertise on how to secure Endpoints, Identities, Apps and Data with Microsoft 365 Defender, Intune, Entra and Purview.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You can design an entire architecture that protects the corporate data and prevent data loss.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You are an expert in one or more Microsoft (365) solutions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise with Defender for Cloud and/or Microsoft Sentinel.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have experience and/or a talent to deliver results-driven workshops with the customer to capture requirements, explain the new way of working that can be realized with out-of-the-box M365, and the benefits that can be realized.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise or affinity with the Microsoft Power low-code Platform or Ometa to further automate and increase productivity in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You’re ready to drive change and bring creative tech ideas to life.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You’re either proficient in Dutch or French (or you want to learn) and fluent in English.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Bonus-points] MS certified (or willing to obtain). Certifications in scope: SC-100, SC-300, SC-400, MS-102, MS-203 etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you do not feel fully confident that you meet the requirements above, please don’t worry. Just apply. Together we’ll discover what you can bring to the table, in which role you would fit best and how you could potentially grow at Devoteam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our promises to you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;As a digital native you will have a positive impact at top organizations in Belgium.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Direct access to the Microsoft organization and programs thanks to our global partnership.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prepare to inspire and be inspired by other Devoteamers in tech communities.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We enable local and international collaboration and exchange with other tech leaders and specialists, knowledge sharing, peer-to-peer coaching.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A personalized career plan with training offers in soft- &amp;amp; hard skills and certifications aligned to your needs &amp;amp; expertise.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our servant leadership supports opportunities to grow your personal brand through blogs, keynote sessions, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;#techies in our minds, #creatives in our hearts, #change in our DNA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why choose us?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cutting-edge Technology&lt;/strong&gt;: Embrace the latest advancements in IT and digital technologies as we constantly innovate to stay ahead of the competition. Our commitment to adopting state-of-the-art tools and methodologies ensures that you'll work on projects at the forefront of the industry.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Entrepreneur mindset&lt;/strong&gt;: We value our people over processes. You will develop and grow in an agile and ambitious company where it’s okay to take risks, make mistakes and change plans to find transformative solutions. At the same time, you will learn from the best, building relationships and skills that will last your entire career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Endless Learning Opportunities&lt;/strong&gt;: We value personal and professional growth. Through workshops, conferences, and certifications, we offer the resources needed to expand your skill set and reach new heights in your career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect with amazing people&lt;/strong&gt;: You will become part of a network of +10,000 Devoteamers spread over 20 countries.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborative Culture&lt;/strong&gt;: Teamwork is at the heart of our organisation. You'll be working side by side with a diverse group of IT experts who share your passion for excellence and will inspire you to think outside the box.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impactful Projects&lt;/strong&gt;: Tackle real-world challenges that matter! From revolutionising business processes to developing innovative solutions, you'll have the chance to make a genuine and positive impact on our clients and the community.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work-Life Balance&lt;/strong&gt;: We believe in a healthy work-life balance, ensuring that you have time to unwind, pursue your hobbies, and spend quality time with loved ones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inspiring and eco-friendly workplace&lt;/strong&gt;: We just moved to an amazing new building. We believe an inspiring workspace fuels creativity and fosters a positive work culture, allowing our employees to reach their full potential. The Wings building is also designed with eco-friendly features and energy-efficient systems. By reducing our ecological footprint, we are contributing to a greener future and aligning our business practices with our environmental values. The building is also very easily accessible by public transportation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive package&lt;/strong&gt;: We offer a competitive salary package with additional benefits like a company car, smartphone, medical insurance, pension plan, net allowance, laptop, meal vouchers, etc. We review our salary grid twice a year to ensure we are in line with the market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Devoteam, we combine strong values – respect, frankness, ambition, entrepreneurship &amp;amp; collaboration - with a fun environment that empowers you to innovate and succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan 3 , 1831 Machelen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 201-500&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10402"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="Security"/>
    <category term="M365"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10055</id>
    <title>Cloud Solution Architect (Sopra Steria)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.363302+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Sopra Steria&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Frédéric La Roche, Recruiter – Sopra Steria Benelux SA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Brussels and Flanders (Culliganlaan 3, 1831 Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 30/06/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sky’s the limit with cloud computing, so you’ll need to use skills of virtualization, containerization, and orchestration using tools like Kubernetes and Docker to design, deploy, and manage cloud-based solutions. We pride ourselves on our secure, compliant, efficient and well-optimized cloud solutions. You’ll feel at home working with cloud-native development, serverless architectures, and DevOps practices. To take cloud adoption to its fullest extent, you’ll use your analytical and governance skills, problem-solving abilities, and cross-functional team collaboration to drive innovation and efficiency in cloud environments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pave the way for cloud adoption and digital transformation with Microsoft Azure’s suite of virtual machines, storage solutions, networking, and databases. Problem-solving, collaboration with cross-functional teams and designing scalable solutions are going to be your key skills. You’ll also familiarize yourself with monitoring tools, and cost management to deliver the continuous integration and delivery, as well as implementing security best practices, quality and compliance that Sopra Steria is known for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our Architects have the vision and leadership skills to make daring IT decisions that can make digital transformation a reality. Your ability to collaborate across teams and departments and your flexibility to adopt new technologies will help you enhance system performance, scalability, and security. Fulfil your vision at Sopra Steria, and align it with our business development goals. As a Sopra Steria Architect, you’ll have successful projects in your portfolio that can demonstrate your excellent problem solving skills and commitment to continuous learning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re seeking passionate colleagues who are eager to push the boundaries in digital transformation and technology consulting. At Sopra Steria, you’ll have the opportunity to grow your skills in a constructive, collaborative team environment, working on impactful projects that drive change for our clients. If you thrive on challenge and meet (most of) the qualifications below, we look forward to your application!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll have knowledge and experience of the following:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s or Master’s&amp;nbsp; degree in computer science or a relevant equivalent&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Designing, implementing and supporting cloud projects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Brown- and greenfield approaches&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Azure cloud technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analysis of complex problems and tackling them with a commercial mindset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Digital innovation and transformation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Business mindset and creating new opportunity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;(Pre)Sales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fluent in English and Dutch/French&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we can offer you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a member of one of Europe’s largest digital solutions providers, you’ll benefit from extensive career development opportunities, both local and international. At the Sopra Steria Academy, you’ll be part of a dynamic network of 56,000 professionals at all stages of their careers. With a wide array of offices to explore, you can find your ideal location and take the next step in your career.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ll become a part of a major Tech player in Europe recognized for its consulting, digital services, and software development. On top of that, you’ll join the Business Line DPS (Digital Platform Services) and join the team of infrastructure and architecture experts: hybrid systems engineers, network and security engineers, Linux consultants, cloud native engineers and cloud solution architects.&lt;br&gt;Our teams help our clients with data center management and data center setup and maintenance. We offer on-premise and cloud solutions, both public and private. This is because we believe in a solution that fits our customers' unique context and business strategy. Often that is a healthy combination of cloud and on-premise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our employees are known for making bold choices and delivering results. Work among high-level professionals at the forefront of corporate software solutions and innovation at Europe’s Leading Digital Service Provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We offer a generous employee benefits package that includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A variety of perks, such as mobility options (including a company car), insurance coverage, meal vouchers, eco-cheques, and more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continuous learning opportunities through the Sopra Steria Academy to support your career development.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to connect with fellow Sopra Steria colleagues at various team events.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;People are the cornerstone of our success. That’s why we aspire to be bolder together. Our goal is to build high-functioning teams and healthy team environments that inspire and help each other to deliver excellence for each of our customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excited about this job opportunity? Ready to shape the world with us? Great! We are looking forward to your application!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to know what happens next?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recruitment process typically begins with the first step, where the recruiter screens candidates based on their qualifications and fit for the role. This is followed by the second step, where candidates undergo more in-depth evaluations, including technical assessments and an interview with the capacity manager to assess both technical skills and team compatibility. The third step involves the company reviewing feedback and aligning on a potential offer. Finally, in the final step, the candidate receives a formal job offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;______&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sopra Steria is an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will be considered for employment without regard to age, ancestry, nationality, color, family or medical leave, gender identity or expression, genetic information, immigration status, marital status, medical condition, national origin, physical or mental disability, political affiliation, protected veteran or military status, race, ethnicity, religion, gender (including pregnancy), sexual orientation or any other characteristic protected by applicable local laws, regulations and ordinances. We foster a work environment that is inclusive and respectful of all differences.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 48&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 501-1000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10055"/>
    <category term="Cloud"/>
    <category term="DevOps"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10004</id>
    <title>Cloud System Engineer (Sopra Steria)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.363201+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Sopra Steria&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Frédéric La Roche, Recruiter – Sopra Steria Benelux SA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Brussels and Flanders (Culliganlaan 3, 1831 Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on 22/08/2025, last change 22/08/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sky’s the limit with cloud computing, so you’ll need to use skills of virtualization, containerization, and orchestration using tools like Kubernetes and Docker to design, deploy, and manage cloud-based solutions. We pride ourselves on our secure, compliant, efficient and well-optimized cloud solutions. You’ll feel at home working with cloud-native development, serverless architectures, and DevOps practices. To take cloud adoption to its fullest extent, you’ll use your analytical and governance skills, problem-solving abilities, and cross-functional team collaboration to drive innovation and efficiency in cloud environments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keeping our systems running smoothly and optimally will be your ultimate goal as our (Cloud) System Engineer. Your days will consist of automating and maintaining our systems as well as developing scripts that optimize our infrastructure and align cloud systems to always serve our business goals. You’ll use your expertise in cloud platforms (Azure &amp;amp; AWS), automation frameworks, containerization, virtualization, networking, and security practices to drive digital transformation. Our goal is to build reliable and cost-efficient systems. As a (Cloud) System Engineer, you’ll make it happen by designing, implementing, and supporting scalable cloud environments, streamlining deployment processes and reducing manual interventions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re seeking passionate colleagues who are eager to push the boundaries in digital transformation and technology consulting. At Sopra Steria, you’ll have the opportunity to grow your skills in a constructive, collaborative team environment, working on impactful projects that drive change for our clients. If you thrive on challenge and meet (most of) the qualifications below, we look forward to your application!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll have knowledge and experience of the following:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s&amp;nbsp;or Master’s degree in computer science or a relevant equivalent&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5 years of experience in infrastructure projects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eperience with cloud services such as Microsoft Azure, AzureAD, EMS, Office365, AWS etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Broad knowledge of networking, system and information architectures, storage concepts, virtualization, containers, automation, Microsoft Azure, Office 365, security and management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scripting and automation: Powershell, VBSript, Bash, Ansible etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with methodologies such as project management, ITIL, etc. or are willing to get certified&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English and Dutch/French&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we can offer you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a member of one of Europe’s largest digital solutions providers, you’ll benefit from extensive career development opportunities, both local and international. At the Sopra Steria Academy, you’ll be part of a dynamic network of 56,000 professionals at all stages of their careers. With a wide array of offices to explore, you can find your ideal location and take the next step in your career.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ll become a part of a major Tech player in Europe recognized for its consulting, digital services, and software development. On top of that, you’ll join the Business Line DPS (Digital Platform Services) and join the team of infrastructure and architecture experts: hybrid systems engineers, network and security engineers, Linux consultants, cloud native engineers and cloud solution architects.&lt;br&gt;Our teams help our clients with data center management and data center setup and maintenance. We offer on-premise and cloud solutions, both public and private. This is because we believe in a solution that fits our customers' unique context and business strategy. Often that is a healthy combination of cloud and on-premise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our employees are known for making bold choices and delivering results. Work among high-level professionals at the forefront of corporate software solutions and innovation at Europe’s Leading Digital Service Provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We offer a generous employee benefits package that includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A variety of perks, such as mobility options (including a company car), insurance coverage, meal vouchers, eco-cheques, and more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continuous learning opportunities through the Sopra Steria Academy to support your career development.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to connect with fellow Sopra Steria colleagues at various team events.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;People are the cornerstone of our success. That’s why we aspire to be bolder together. Our goal is to build high-functioning teams and healthy team environments that inspire and help each other to deliver excellence for each of our customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excited about this job opportunity? Ready to shape the world with us? Great! We are looking forward to your application!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to know what happens next?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recruitment process typically begins with the first step, where the recruiter screens candidates based on their qualifications and fit for the role. This is followed by the second step, where candidates undergo more in-depth evaluations, including technical assessments and an interview with the capacity manager to assess both technical skills and team compatibility. The third step involves the company reviewing feedback and aligning on a potential offer. Finally, in the final step, the candidate receives a formal job offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;______&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sopra Steria is an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will be considered for employment without regard to age, ancestry, nationality, color, family or medical leave, gender identity or expression, genetic information, immigration status, marital status, medical condition, national origin, physical or mental disability, political affiliation, protected veteran or military status, race, ethnicity, religion, gender (including pregnancy), sexual orientation or any other characteristic protected by applicable local laws, regulations and ordinances. We foster a work environment that is inclusive and respectful of all differences.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 48&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 501-1000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10004"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="Amazon Web Services (AWS)"/>
    <category term="Microsoft 365 / Office 365"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/12386</id>
    <title>M365 Solution &amp; Change Analyst/Architect (Devoteam)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.363100+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Bob Cobben, Senior Talent Acquisition Specialist – Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Machelen (Culliganlaan 3, 1831 Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on 04/08/2025, last change 04/08/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like these keywords, you’ll love this role:&lt;br&gt;#M365 #SharePoint #Teams #Yammer #PowerPlatform #Adoption #Change&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s more fundamental in IT than a Digital Workplace that is fully adopted by end users?&lt;br&gt;Develop, design, and build the future with us as a Microsoft 365 Workplace Solution Architect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will be part of the “Data Integrated Digital Workplace” practice with an in-depth expertise combination on Microsoft’s Modern Workplace (SharePoint and MS 365), Data Business Intelligence (SQL &amp;amp; Azure Data Warehousing and Power BI),and low-code development frameworks on Azure.&lt;br&gt;You and the team share the vision and passion “to create &amp;amp; develop Digital Workplaces with true Business value &amp;amp; adoption” by offering end-users integrated platforms where they find, get pushed and can act upon all the right information, data and documents, at the right time and in the right business context.&lt;br&gt;You will work with Client’s Business &amp;amp; Technical employees to capture, discuss, create, build, deliver &amp;amp; verify solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Profile&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have a broad view on the entire Microsoft 365 “Modern Workplace” portfolio including Teams &amp;amp; SharePoint&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have experience and/or a talent to deliver results-driven workshops with the customer to capture requirements, explain the new way of working that can be realized with out-of-the-box M365, and the benefits that can be realized.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have experience and/or a talent to work with in-depth technical experts to get the defined solutions created.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have experience and/or a talent to guide customers in adopting the solutions on your own or with specialized adoption and change managers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise or affinity with the Microsoft Security, Compliance &amp;amp; Identity solutions to secure customers’ Modern Workplace&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise or affinity with Microsoft Defender and Intune to secure customers’ Endpoints of their Modern Workplace&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise or affinity with the Microsoft Power low-code Platform to further automate and increase productivity in customers’ Modern Workplace&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise or affinity with Front-end and/or Back-end(.NET) development of solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You’re ready to drive change and bring creative tech ideas to life.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You’re either proficient in Dutch or French (or you want to learn) and fluent in English.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Bonus-points] MS 365 certified (or willing to obtain). Certifications in scope: MS-900, MS-600, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Bonus-points] MS Power Platform certified (or willing to obtain). Certifications in scope: PL-900, PL-200, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Bonus-points] MS Security, Compliance &amp;amp; Identity certified (or willing to obtain). Certifications in scope: SC-900, SC-300, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you do not feel fully confident that you meet the requirements above, please don’t worry. Just apply. Together we’ll discover what you can bring to the table, in which role you would fit best and how you could potentially grow at Devoteam.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our promises to you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;As a digital native you will have a positive impact at top organizations in Belgium.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Direct access to the Microsoft organization and programs thanks to our global partnership.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prepare to inspire and be inspired by other Devoteamers in tech communities.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We enable local and international collaboration and exchange with other tech leaders and specialists, knowledge sharing, peer-to-peer coaching.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A personalized career plan with training offers in soft- &amp;amp; hard skills and certifications aligned to your needs &amp;amp; expertise.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Our servant leadership supports opportunities to grow your personal brand through blogs, keynote sessions, and more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;#techies in our minds, #creatives in our hearts, #change in our DNA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why choose us?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cutting-edge Technology&lt;/strong&gt;: Embrace the latest advancements in IT and digital technologies as we constantly innovate to stay ahead of the competition. Our commitment to adopting state-of-the-art tools and methodologies ensures that you'll work on projects at the forefront of the industry.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Entrepreneur mindset&lt;/strong&gt;: We value our people over processes. You will develop and grow in an agile and ambitious company where it’s okay to take risks, make mistakes and change plans to find transformative solutions. At the same time, you will learn from the best, building relationships and skills that will last your entire career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Endless Learning Opportunities&lt;/strong&gt;: We value personal and professional growth. Through workshops, conferences, and certifications, we offer the resources needed to expand your skill set and reach new heights in your career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect with amazing people&lt;/strong&gt;: You will become part of a network of +10,000 Devoteamers spread over 20 countries.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborative Culture&lt;/strong&gt;: Teamwork is at the heart of our organisation. You'll be working side by side with a diverse group of IT experts who share your passion for excellence and will inspire you to think outside the box.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impactful Projects&lt;/strong&gt;: Tackle real-world challenges that matter! From revolutionising business processes to developing innovative solutions, you'll have the chance to make a genuine and positive impact on our clients and the community.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work-Life Balance&lt;/strong&gt;: We believe in a healthy work-life balance, ensuring that you have time to unwind, pursue your hobbies, and spend quality time with loved ones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inspiring and eco-friendly workplace&lt;/strong&gt;: We just moved to an amazing new building. We believe an inspiring workspace fuels creativity and fosters a positive work culture, allowing our employees to reach their full potential. The Wings building is also designed with eco-friendly features and energy-efficient systems. By reducing our ecological footprint, we are contributing to a greener future and aligning our business practices with our environmental values. The building is also very easily accessible by public transportation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive package&lt;/strong&gt;: We offer a competitive salary package with additional benefits like a company car, smartphone, medical insurance, pension plan, net allowance, laptop, meal vouchers, etc. We review our salary grid twice a year to ensure we are in line with the market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Devoteam, we combine strong values – respect, frankness, ambition, entrepreneurship &amp;amp; collaboration - with a fun environment that empowers you to innovate and succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan 3 , 1831 Machelen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 201-500&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/12386"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="Security"/>
    <category term="Pre-Sales Consulting"/>
    <category term="M365"/>
    <category term="Power Platform"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/11647</id>
    <title>Functioneel Analist (Madison Recruitment)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.363000+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Madison Recruitment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Piet Leemans, Markering Strategist &amp;amp; Process Analyst – Madison IT &amp;amp; Engineering Recruitment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Berchem , Antwerpen (Berchem , Antwerpen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 20/03/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Voor onze klant, gekende speler in &lt;strong&gt;Antwerpen&lt;/strong&gt;, ben ik op zoek naar een &lt;strong&gt;Functioneel Analist&lt;/strong&gt;. Deze onderneming is niet blind voor de digitale stroomversnelling en investeert al jaren fors in de nieuwste technologieën, wat zich consequent vertaalt in de kwaliteit van hun dienstverlening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Ze zetten volop in op automatisering via hun &lt;strong&gt;strategisch intern ontwikkelde core banking software&lt;/strong&gt;. Binnen hun ‘state-of-the-art” IT-team tellen we dan ook maar liefst &lt;strong&gt;160 collega’s&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Als Functioneel Analist vertaal je complexe bedrijfsbehoeften naar bruikbare data-oplossingen. Samen met je collega’s werk je aan innovatieve, schaalbare oplossingen die bijdragen aan de strategische doelen. Je denkt actief mee over verbeteringen en nieuwe mogelijkheden, waardoor je altijd een stap vooruit blijft. Dankzij je analytisch inzicht en gestructureerde aanpak zorg je ervoor dat data-initiatieven zowel technisch haalbaar als praktisch toepasbaar en impactvol zijn.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Profiel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Je behaalde een relevant &lt;strong&gt;masterdiploma&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Je hebt &lt;strong&gt;minstens 5 jaar relevante ervaring binnen een gelijkaardige functie&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Je beschikt over een analytisch denkvermogen, sterke communicatieve vaardigheden en neemt initiatief&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Je bent fan van &lt;strong&gt;multidisciplinaire teams&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Technische kennis:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Databases en SQL&lt;/strong&gt;: basiskennis van relationele databases en SQL om datasets te analyseren en query’s te maken.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;BI- en Reporting Tools&lt;/strong&gt; (tools zoals &lt;strong&gt;Power BI&lt;/strong&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Datamodellering&lt;/strong&gt; (concepten zoals dimensionele modellering en normalisatie)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Procesmodellering: &lt;strong&gt;BPMN&lt;/strong&gt; en &lt;strong&gt;UML&lt;/strong&gt; om workflows en processtromen in kaart te brengen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Ervaring met agile werkmethodieken (&lt;strong&gt;Scrum, Kanban&lt;/strong&gt;) en tools zoals &lt;strong&gt;Azure DevOps&lt;/strong&gt; of &lt;strong&gt;GitHub&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Vaardigheid in het opstellen van &lt;strong&gt;user stories&lt;/strong&gt; en &lt;strong&gt;acceptatiecriteria&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Aanbod&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Competitief loon dat wordt aangevuld met &lt;strong&gt;bedrijfswagen&lt;/strong&gt;, maaltijdcheques, netto vergoeding, hospitalisatieverzekering, groepsverzekering, ecocheques...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Prachtig hoofdkantoor in Berchem met &lt;strong&gt;bedrijfsrestaurant&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Organisatie met zeer weinig verloop&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;em&gt;#LI-ED1&lt;/em&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Frankrijklei&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 174&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 11 - 50&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Staffing &amp;amp; Recruiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/11647"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term="Power BI"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10787</id>
    <title>Fullstack.NET-ontwikkelaar expert (Digitaal Vlaanderen)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.362895+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Digitaal Vlaanderen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: dierik liagre, IT recruiter – Digitaal Vlaanderen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Gent (Maria Hendrikaplein 70, 9000 Gent)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 09/05/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inleiding&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bij het agentschap Digitaal Vlaanderen gaan we op zoek naar een fullstack .NET-ontwikkelaar expert&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;ter versterking van onze Data Platform afdeling binnen het team Data-integratietoepassingen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ben jij op zoek naar een nieuwe uitdaging waarbij je als .NET-ontwikkelaar expert wil meewerken aan het ontwikkelen en in dienst nemen van toepassingen ter ondersteuning van ons dataintegratieplatform? Dan ben jij misschien wel onze ideale kandidaat!&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Waar kom je terecht?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Digitaal Vlaanderen is het digitaliseringsagentschap van de Vlaamse overheid. We ondersteunen en begeleiden Vlaamse en lokale overheden in hun digitale transformatie en hun zoektocht naar de overheid van morgen. Voor hen ontwikkelen we hightech oplossingen, bouwstenen en platformen, van loket- en frontoffice-oplossingen tot ICT, beveiliging en data. Digitaal Vlaanderen behoort tot de frontrunners van de digitalisering in Europa. Op het vlak van open gelinkte data en open datastandaarden zijn we toonaangevend. We zijn grensverleggend in het gebruik van AI en we voeren een innovatief, duurzaam en inclusief beleid. Dat maakt van ons één van de grootste en boeiendste werkgevers voor ICT-talent in Vlaanderen. En jij kan daar deel van uitmaken.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Je komt terecht in het team Data-integratietoepassingen binnen de afdeling Data Platform. Dit team bouwt en neemt toepassingen in beheer die ondersteunend werken voor het centraal gegevensuitwisselingsplatform. Via deze tools ontzorgen we partners bij het aansluiten, publiceren en beheren van data op het platform. We zorgen dat deze tools duurzaam en op een veilige en gestandaardiseerde manier kunnen ingezet worden. Op het centrale gegevensuitwisselingsplatform bieden we zowel open als gesloten overheidsdata aan. Deze data wordt op een uniforme, gestandaardiseerde, betrouwbare, veilige manier en conform de wetgeving ter beschikking gesteld waarbij de principes van dataveiligheid &amp;amp; informatieclassificatie toegepast worden.&lt;br&gt;We treden op als een betrouwbare partner om de continuïteit en kwaliteit van de data-uitwisseling te waarborgen. Als .NET-ontwikkelaar krijg je bij ons de kans om te werken met state-of-the-art technologie en kan je je technische vaardigheden verder ontwikkelen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Het team werkt voornamelijk vanuit het VAC te Gent (Virginie Lovelinggebouw). Af en toe verplaatsen we ons naar het VAC te Brussel (Herman Teirlinckgebouw).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wat zal je moeten doen?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Als full-stack ontwikkelaar expert&amp;nbsp;ben je verantwoordelijk voor het ontwikkelen en aanpassen van software op basis van user stories.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je schrijft&amp;nbsp;efficiënte en onderhoudbare code, waarborgt kwalitatieve en veilige softwareoplossingen, en documenteert technische aspecten.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je schrijft&amp;nbsp;testen zoals unit-testen, integratie-testen en API-testen, ondersteunt het team met je technische expertise en controleert de kwaliteit van nieuwe code via code reviews.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Daarnaast coach je&amp;nbsp;collega-ontwikkelaars, bewaak je de planning en deadlines van de technische backlog en stimuleer je continu de kennisontwikkeling en maturiteit binnen het team.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je neemt&amp;nbsp;actief deel aan agile ceremonies zoals stand-ups, sprint planningen en retrospectives.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je werkt&amp;nbsp;nauw samen met andere teamleden zoals architecten, ontwikkelaars, analisten, testers en product owners, communiceert vlot met alle teamleden en handelt proactief.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Je verleent&amp;nbsp;3rd line support bij incidenten of klantenvragen en rapporteert aan een technisch architect, een functioneel of business analist, een project manager en de product owner.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Naar wie zijn wij op zoek?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je beschikt&amp;nbsp;over een hogere opleiding (Master of Bachelor) met een technische/engineering of bedrijfseconomische achtergrond, of je bent gelijkwaardig door ervaring.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je hebt grondige kennis en minimaal 6 jaar aantoonbare ervaring in Azure en Azure DevOps Pipelines.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We zoeken&amp;nbsp;een ontwikkelaar die het .NET Framework door en door kent en graag aan de slag gaat met front-end technologieën zoals Vue.js en Typescript.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je kan technische analyses maken op basis van input van de business.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je bent&amp;nbsp;een teamplayer die graag in groepsverband code schrijft en zorgt dat de software kwalitatief en onderhoudsvriendelijk blijft.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Technologieën zoals .NET Framework, .NET Core, OAuth, Bicep en OpenAPI zijn je niet onbekend en tools zoals Microsoft SQL Server, Visual Studio en Postman beheers je voortreffelijk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ervaring&amp;nbsp;met geografische systemen (OpenLayers, QGis, Geonetwork) en geografische concepten (projectiesystemen, DCAT) is een pluspunt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wat kunnen wij jou bieden?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vlaanderen connect. biedt een contract van onbepaalde duur en een competitief salarispakket met:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een aantrekkelijke brutoverloning&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een bonussysteem op basis van vast te leggen doelstellingen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een mobiliteitsbudget&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maaltijdcheques van 8 euro/dag (eigen bijdrage 1,09 euro/dag)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een forfaitaire onkostenvergoeding&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een hospitalisatieverzekering (je kan gezinsleden aansluiten)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een groepsverzekering&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een arbeidsongevallenverzekering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een opleidingsbudget&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een laptop&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een smartphone met abonnementsformule&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Thuiswerkmiddelen en mogelijkheden tot thuiswerk&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mogelijkheid tot kinderopvang tijdens alle schoolvakanties aan een voordelig tarief.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bij Vlaanderen connect. is een gezonde balans tussen werk en privé belangrijk: een werkweek van&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;38 uur, 28 dagen verlof en extra wettelijke feestdagen (11/07, 02/11, 15/11 en 26/12).&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Verder werken wij met flexibele werkuren en bieden wij ook de mogelijkheid tot thuiswerken.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Werken via Vlaanderen connect.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Je wordt tewerkgesteld via Vlaanderen connect., de ICT-strategische dienstverlener van de Vlaamse overheid. Bij Vlaanderen connect. word je voor onbepaalde duur ter beschikking gesteld aan Digitaal Vlaanderen. Hierbij ontvang je een contract van onbepaalde duur.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Werken voor Vlaanderen connect. betekent werken in een organisatie met boeiende en uitdagende IT-functies én de mogelijkheid om mee je schouders te zetten in het uitbouwen van een digitaal en slagkrachtig Vlaanderen.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verder biedt werken voor Vlaanderen connect. tal van voordelen. Je werkt bij entiteiten van de Vlaamse overheid of bij lokale besturen voor lange termijn. Zo kan je meewerken&amp;nbsp; aan een digitale en slagkrachtige overheid, voor burgers en ondernemers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Daarnaast kan je doorgroeien en jezelf ontwikkelen door het enorme potentieel aan uitdagende functies via Vlaanderen connect. bij de Vlaamse overheid en de lokale besturen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Havenlaan&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 15&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 501-1000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Government Administration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10787"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term=".NET"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="Visual Studio"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/5458</id>
    <title>Senior Adobe Campaign Developer (Capgemini Belgium)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.362789+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Capgemini Belgium&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Stéphanie Gérard, Talent acquisition specialist – Capgemini Belgium&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Hybrid work location (home, client site, Capgemini office), work up to 70% from home (Hybrid work location (home, client site, Capgemini office), work up to 70% from home)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 24/07/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your job&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Direct contact with client’s Business and IT teams to provide them technical solutions based on their business requirements.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Analyze the requirements, design, and Implement data models, technical workflows.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Conduct code reviews, test new capabilities and documentations along with participating in application architecture and design&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Coordinating long-term cross-platform objectives to meet business goals&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Defect &amp;amp; incident resolution, with reporting to (upper) management&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Documentation on existing/new set-ups, including training of other team members&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your passport&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;4+ years of experience in End-to-end implementation experience with Adobe Campaign Classic and/or Standard&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Work with clients to understand their business requirements, design and develop Adobe Campaign Classic and/or Standard solutions to meet customer business needs&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Extensive experience in building technical workflows for data import &amp;amp; export, reports, monitoring and alerts in Adobe Campaign Classic and/or Standard&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Expertise and experience in creating Adobe Campaign entities like Data Schema, Input forms, Navigation hierarchies, Web applications, Delivery templates&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Advanced knowledge in implement SOAP/REST API, delivery templates for real time email communications&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Implementing content personalization and dynamic content within emails&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Deep knowledge in JavaScript, HTML, CSS, XML, JSON&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Expertise and Experience in SQL (Oracle / SQL Server / PostgreSQL)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Excellent knowledge of Marketing Management across multiple Channels (email, SMS, push)&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Experience package migration, access management and monitoring of platform&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Good to have experience in integrating Adobe Campaign to product such as AEM, Adobe Target, Adobe Audience Manager, Adobe Analytics, Adobe Experience platform&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Deep understanding of Adobe Campaign architectures&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are keen to work in international environment&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;You are fluent in English, NL or FR is a huge plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Adobe Campaign Developer certification(s) are a strong plus&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why choose Capgemini?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Because you want to contribute to impactful projects for Fortune 500 companies&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Because you’re looking for an organization that’s committed to sustainability&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Because you want to be part of an active and growing team that shares insights and experiences non-stop&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Because we reward your enthusiasm with a competitive salary and package&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Because you share our passion for creative work and get a kick out of complexity&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Bessenveldstraat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 501-1000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/5458"/>
    <category term="JavaScript"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term="CSS"/>
    <category term="HTML"/>
    <category term="SOAP"/>
    <category term="Oracle"/>
    <category term="PostgreSQL"/>
    <category term="XML / XSL / XSLT"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10632</id>
    <title>Inhouse BI Specialist (PowerBI, SQL) (Madison Recruitment)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.362682+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Madison Recruitment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Piet Leemans, Markering Strategist &amp;amp; Process Analyst – Madison IT &amp;amp; Engineering Recruitment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Mechelen (2800, Mechelen, Antwerpen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on 25/08/2025, last change 25/08/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deze partner is actief als dienstverlener voor bedrijven in de telecomsector. Ze zijn gelegen te Rumst. Momenteel kijken ze uit naar een BI Specialist om hun schat aan data efficiënt te gaan gebruiken.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Als BI specialist ga je in nauwe samenwerking met Business Analysts en andere afdelingen inzicht verkrijgen in de behoeften in verschillende domeinen. Hierna ga je de requirements mee opstellen en prioriteren.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verder ga je een BI model uitwerken:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Datastromen opvolgen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bronnen toevoegen aan datawarehouse en vertalen naar datasets&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Rapportages opmaken&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Profiel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je hebt een goede kennis van &lt;strong&gt;Power BI &amp;amp; SQL&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Minimaal twee jaar ervaring&lt;/strong&gt; in een relevante functie&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kennis van &lt;strong&gt;Python&lt;/strong&gt; is een plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Je bent zeer &lt;strong&gt;communicatief in het Nederlands en Engels&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naast een marktconform salaris in lijn met je ervaring krijg je een aantal mooie voordelen!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wagen met tankkaart&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dagvergoeding&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Groeps- en hospitalisatieverzekering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Laptop en Gsm&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Meteen een contract van onbepaalde duur&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een zeer uitdagende omgeving waar je persoonlijke ontwikkeling mee wordt ondersteund&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;CAO 90 bonus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Interesse?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Dan mag je je CV alvast doorsturen via Editx&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;#LI-EV1&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Frankrijklei&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 174&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 11 - 50&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Staffing &amp;amp; Recruiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10632"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term="Python"/>
    <category term="Power BI"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/11071</id>
    <title>Product Owner Data-Integratie (Digitaal Vlaanderen)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.362561+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Digitaal Vlaanderen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: dierik liagre, IT recruiter – Digitaal Vlaanderen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Gent (Maria Hendrikaplein 70, 9000 Gent)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on 22/08/2025, last change 22/08/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inleiding&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bij het agentschap Digitaal Vlaanderen gaan we op zoek naar een Product Owner&lt;strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;ter versterking van het team Data-integratie subteam Data-Integratiediensten.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ben jij op zoek naar een nieuwe uitdaging waarbij je als Product Owner wil mee bouwen aan de producten en diensten binnen Data-integratie, om zo verschillende types datastromen van diverse domeinen mogelijk te maken, dan ben jij misschien wel onze ideale kandidaat!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Binnen Data-integratie zoeken wij een Product Owner die zich in eerste instantie zal richten op de geowebdiensten en bij uitbreiding op andere domeinen binnen het subteam. Deze geografische diensten (API’s) richten zich specifiek op het verspreiden van ruimtelijke gegevens (&lt;a href="https://www.vlaanderen.be/digitaal-vlaanderen/onze-diensten-en-platformen/geografische-webdiensten"&gt;Geografische webdiensten | Vlaanderen.be)&lt;/a&gt;. Deze diensten worden gebruikt in bedrijfsprocessen en verstrekken informatie omtrent onze (ruimtelijke) omgeving. Het gaat onder andere over de geobasisregisters, luchtfoto’s en historische kaarten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ze worden gebruikt door softwareontwikkelaars voor online toepassingen en software, maar ook door o.a. GIS-experten, beleidsmedewerkers, ruimtelijke planners, wetenschappers in standaard desktop en online GIS-toepassingen.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Om aan de diversiteit van het gebruik te kunnen voldoen, is interoperabiliteit en standaardisatie van deze services ontzettend belangrijk. Daarom voldoen deze services aan internationale standaarden zoals die van Open Geopsatial (OGC), ISO en W3C en implementatie richtlijnen zoals de Europese INSPIRE-directive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Waar kom je terecht?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Digitalisering&amp;nbsp;staat&amp;nbsp;hoger dan&amp;nbsp;ooit op de&amp;nbsp;Vlaamse agenda.&amp;nbsp;Digitaal Vlaanderen&amp;nbsp;beantwoordt&amp;nbsp;aan&amp;nbsp;deze&amp;nbsp;nood. We&amp;nbsp;willen de motor&amp;nbsp;zijn&amp;nbsp;voor de&amp;nbsp;digitale&amp;nbsp;transformatie van&amp;nbsp;overheden in Vlaanderen.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Digitaal Vlaanderen is&amp;nbsp;een&amp;nbsp;geëngageerde,&amp;nbsp;klantgerichte&amp;nbsp;businesspartner&amp;nbsp;voor&amp;nbsp;Vlaamse&amp;nbsp;overheidsdiensten&amp;nbsp;en&amp;nbsp;lokale&amp;nbsp;overheden. We&amp;nbsp;bieden hen&amp;nbsp;een&amp;nbsp;voorsprong door&amp;nbsp;digitale&amp;nbsp;oplossingen&amp;nbsp;aan&amp;nbsp;te&amp;nbsp;bieden die&amp;nbsp;binnen&amp;nbsp;een breed&amp;nbsp;en&amp;nbsp;schaalbaar&amp;nbsp;ecosysteem&amp;nbsp;te&amp;nbsp;situeren&amp;nbsp;zijn. Een&amp;nbsp;intelligente&amp;nbsp;en&amp;nbsp;wendbare&amp;nbsp;dienstverlening&amp;nbsp;staat&amp;nbsp;hierbij steeds&amp;nbsp;centraal.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;Je zal terecht komen bij het team “Data-integratiediensten” en samenwerken met experten op het vlak van databeheer, datatransformatie en IT-architecten binnen Digitaal Vlaanderen waarbij je als Product Owner mee vorm geeft aan een framework voor het aanbieden van deze API’s en het bewaken van de functionaliteit, schaalbaarheid en beheerbaarheid van het systeem.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Als Product Owner ben je verantwoordelijk voor de inhoudelijke uitvoering van business cases en/of de end-to-end product life cycle. Hierbij verdiep je je en begrijp je voor een aantal specifieke producten de exacte vraag, knelpunten, bestaande noden, opportuniteiten en informatiebehoeften van klanten, stakeholders en eindgebruikers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Je bent verantwoordelijk om zicht te houden op de waarde van de producten (inhoudelijk, technisch en functioneel) en detecteert nieuwe productkansen voor de betrokken organisatie en haar partners. Het betreft producten met de nodige complexiteit, afhankelijkheden en interacties. Standaardisatie is een sleutel gegeven bij het opzetten en beheren van deze services.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Je rapporteert regelmatig de voortgang aan je teamcoach en de manager. Je signaleert proactief opportuniteiten om de werking te verbeteren en je werkt actief mee aan optimalisatie- en vernieuwingsprojecten.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Binnen het team zal je initieel de Product Owner worden voor geografische webdiensten.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Je neemt verantwoordelijkheid voor de operationele werking van de diensten, het ter beschikking stellen van nieuwe diensten binnen het bestaande systeem, het toekomstgericht upscalen van het systeem om te voldoen aan de toekomstige noden en het aanbieden van nieuwe types diensten op basis van de evoluerende standaarden en aangereikte use cases.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Je zorgt voor het opstellen van de budgetten en het opvolgen en rapporteren ervan in samenwerking met de financieel verantwoordelijken binnen de organisatie. Later neem je meerdere domeinen voor je rekening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Naar wie zijn wij op zoek?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We zijn op zoek naar iemand met aantoonbare ervaring als Product Owner en ervaring met het nemen van een end-to-end verantwoordelijkheid op productniveau, het uitwerken en mee laten evolueren van inhoudelijke visies en inzichten, het opbouwen/onderhouden van het stakeholdernetwerk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ook het definiëren van eisen, analyseren van bedrijfsprocessen, procesverbetering en re-engineering zijn voor jou niet ongekend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Je hebt ervaring met complexere opdrachten, met een diversiteit aan stakeholders, doelgroepen en hun (soms tegengestelde) behoeften.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Het leiden van werkgroepen en het leiden van diverse projecten schrikken jou niet af.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;Vaktechnische competenties:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je bent analytisch en benadert een vraagstuk vanuit verschillende invalshoeken. Je analyse draagt bij aan een heldere doorstroming en implementatie. Ervaring in analyse (high level, business en functioneel) is dus een toegevoegde waarde.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ervaring met technische applicaties die de basis vormen voor andere systemen is een pluspunt. (bv. ETL, Azure Cloud, OpenAPI, XML).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kennis van geogerelateerde aspecten is een pluspunt.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je legt verbanden en trekt logische conclusies op basis van de beschikbare gegevens om beslissingen te faciliteren en oplossingen uit te denken.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je communiceert met verschillende doelgroepen op een professionele, eerlijke en open manier.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je bent klantgericht, staat open voor (nieuwe) behoeften van de belanghebbenden en je kan hierop creatief anticiperen.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ervaring in projectmanagement is een toegevoegde waarde.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Interoperabiliteit en standaardisatie is voor jou een uitdaging.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Persoonsgebonden competenties:&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We zoeken iemand die een enthousiaste, flexibele teamspeler is die de samenwerking binnen de entiteit, werkgroepen en of projectgroepen kan stimuleren en motiveren.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Het duidelijk stellen van een visie en die ook uitdragen is jou niet vreemd. Je durft ook de nodige beslissingen te nemen.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Verder verwachten we een verbindende doch heldere communicatiestijl waardoor je een team kan&amp;nbsp;ondersteunen en begeleiden als zelfsturend geheel. Daarbij handel je proactief en in het belang van de organisatie. Je bent een betrouwbare partner voor collega’s, stakeholders en opdrachtgevers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Leergierigheid en werken naar de vastgelegde doelstellingen met de nodige zin voor ondernemen en initiatief liggen in lijn met jouw persoonlijkheid. Een probleem is een uitdaging die jij graag oplost.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wat kunnen wij jou bieden?&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vlaanderen connect. biedt een contract van onbepaalde duur en een competitief salarispakket met:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een aantrekkelijke brutoverloning&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een bonussysteem op basis van vast te leggen doelstellingen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een mobiliteitsbudget&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maaltijdcheques van 8 euro/dag (eigen bijdrage 1,09 euro/dag)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een forfaitaire onkostenvergoeding&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een hospitalisatieverzekering (je kan gezinsleden aansluiten)&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een groepsverzekering&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een opleidingsbudget&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een laptop&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een smartphone met abonnementsformule&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Thuiswerkmiddelen en mogelijkheden tot thuiswerk&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mogelijkheid tot kinderopvang tijdens alle schoolvakanties aan een voordelig tarief.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bij Vlaanderen connect. is een gezonde balans tussen werk en privé belangrijk: een werkweek van&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;38 uur, 28 dagen verlof en extra wettelijke feestdagen (11/07, 02/11, 15/11 en 26/12).&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Verder werken wij met flexibele werkuren en bieden wij ook de mogelijkheid tot thuiswerken.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Werken via Vlaanderen connect.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Je wordt tewerkgesteld via Vlaanderen connect., de ICT-strategische dienstverlener van de Vlaamse overheid. Bij Vlaanderen connect. word je voor onbepaalde duur ter beschikking gesteld aan Digitaal Vlaanderen. Hierbij ontvang je een contract van onbepaalde duur.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Werken voor Vlaanderen connect. betekent werken in een organisatie met boeiende en uitdagende IT-functies én de mogelijkheid om mee je schouders te zetten in het uitbouwen van een digitaal en slagkrachtig Vlaanderen.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Verder biedt werken voor Vlaanderen connect. tal van voordelen. Je werkt bij entiteiten van de Vlaamse overheid of bij lokale besturen voor lange termijn. Zo kan je meewerken&amp;nbsp; aan een digitale en slagkrachtige overheid, voor burgers en ondernemers.&amp;nbsp;&lt;br&gt;Daarnaast kan je doorgroeien en jezelf ontwikkelen door het enorme potentieel aan uitdagende functies via Vlaanderen connect. bij de Vlaamse overheid en de lokale besturen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Havenlaan&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 15&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 501-1000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Government Administration&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/11071"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="ETL / Datawarehouse"/>
    <category term="XML / XSL / XSLT"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10403</id>
    <title>Azure Data Engineer (Devoteam)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.362454+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Laurent  Huygens, Talent Acquisition Manager – Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Machelen (3 Cullinganlaan 1831 Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on 15/08/2025, last change 15/08/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like these keywords, you’ll love this role:&lt;br&gt;#M365 #Entra #Defender #Purview #Intune&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s more fundamental in IT these days than a Digital Workplace that is fully secured and compliant by end users?&lt;br&gt;Develop, design, and build the future with us as a Microsoft 365 Workplace Security Architect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a Workplace Security Architect, you know the solutions that can help in increasing the workplace security maturity. You know what Zero-trust is and how you can use Microsoft technology to protect customers against cyberthreats. You will work with Client’s Business &amp;amp; Technical employees to capture, discuss, create, build, deliver &amp;amp; verify solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this position, we’re looking for &lt;strong&gt;all seniority levels&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have a broad view of the Modern Workplace building blocks, from classic solutions to Microsoft 365.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have a broad view of all the Microsoft 365 Defender Solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have expertise on how to secure Endpoints, Identities, Apps and Data with Microsoft 365 Defender, Intune, Entra and Purview.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You can design an entire architecture that protects the corporate data and prevent data loss.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You are an expert in one or more Microsoft (365) solutions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise with Defender for Cloud and/or Microsoft Sentinel.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have experience and/or a talent to deliver results-driven workshops with the customer to capture requirements, explain the new way of working that can be realized with out-of-the-box M365, and the benefits that can be realized.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise or affinity with the Microsoft Power low-code Platform or Ometa to further automate and increase productivity in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You’re ready to drive change and bring creative tech ideas to life.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You’re either proficient in Dutch or French (or you want to learn) and fluent in English.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Bonus-points] MS certified (or willing to obtain). Certifications in scope: SC-100, SC-300, SC-400, MS-102, MS-203 etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you do not feel fully confident that you meet the requirements above, please don’t worry. Just apply. Together we’ll discover what you can bring to the table, in which role you would fit best and how you could potentially grow at Devoteam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our promises to you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;As a digital native you will have a positive impact at top organizations in Belgium.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Direct access to the Microsoft organization and programs thanks to our global partnership.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prepare to inspire and be inspired by other Devoteamers in tech communities.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We enable local and international collaboration and exchange with other tech leaders and specialists, knowledge sharing, peer-to-peer coaching.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A personalized career plan with training offers in soft- &amp;amp; hard skills and certifications aligned to your needs &amp;amp; expertise.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Our servant leadership supports opportunities to grow your personal brand through blogs, keynote sessions, and more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;#techies in our minds, #creatives in our hearts, #change in our DNA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why choose us?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cutting-edge Technology&lt;/strong&gt;: Embrace the latest advancements in IT and digital technologies as we constantly innovate to stay ahead of the competition. Our commitment to adopting state-of-the-art tools and methodologies ensures that you'll work on projects at the forefront of the industry.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Entrepreneur mindset&lt;/strong&gt;: We value our people over processes. You will develop and grow in an agile and ambitious company where it’s okay to take risks, make mistakes and change plans to find transformative solutions. At the same time, you will learn from the best, building relationships and skills that will last your entire career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Endless Learning Opportunities&lt;/strong&gt;: We value personal and professional growth. Through workshops, conferences, and certifications, we offer the resources needed to expand your skill set and reach new heights in your career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect with amazing people&lt;/strong&gt;: You will become part of a network of +10,000 Devoteamers spread over 20 countries.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborative Culture&lt;/strong&gt;: Teamwork is at the heart of our organisation. You'll be working side by side with a diverse group of IT experts who share your passion for excellence and will inspire you to think outside the box.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impactful Projects&lt;/strong&gt;: Tackle real-world challenges that matter! From revolutionising business processes to developing innovative solutions, you'll have the chance to make a genuine and positive impact on our clients and the community.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work-Life Balance&lt;/strong&gt;: We believe in a healthy work-life balance, ensuring that you have time to unwind, pursue your hobbies, and spend quality time with loved ones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inspiring and eco-friendly workplace&lt;/strong&gt;: We just moved to an amazing new building. We believe an inspiring workspace fuels creativity and fosters a positive work culture, allowing our employees to reach their full potential. The Wings building is also designed with eco-friendly features and energy-efficient systems. By reducing our ecological footprint, we are contributing to a greener future and aligning our business practices with our environmental values. The building is also very easily accessible by public transportation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive package&lt;/strong&gt;: We offer a competitive salary package with additional benefits like a company car, smartphone, medical insurance, pension plan, net allowance, laptop, meal vouchers, etc. We review our salary grid twice a year to ensure we are in line with the market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Devoteam, we combine strong values – respect, frankness, ambition, entrepreneurship &amp;amp; collaboration - with a fun environment that empowers you to innovate and succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan 3 , 1831 Machelen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 201-500&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10403"/>
    <category term="Cloud"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="Business Intelligence"/>
    <category term="SSIS"/>
    <category term="Microsoft SQL Server"/>
    <category term="Power BI"/>
    <category term="SSAS / SSRS"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10485</id>
    <title>Analytics Engineer (Datashift)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.362353+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Datashift&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Fred Thiebaut, Recruiter – Datashift&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Mechelen (Oude Brusselsestraat 14, 2800 Mechelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on 28/08/2025, last change 28/08/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Datashift, a rapidly expanding team dedicated to providing data-driven solutions for business challenges, is seeking a talented &lt;strong&gt;Analytics Engineer&lt;/strong&gt; to join us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this role, you will play a crucial part in translating client needs into sustainable data solutions, encompassing ETL processes, Infrastructure as Code, interfaces, and pipelines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Designing data solutions, balancing cost and maintainability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with Data Scientists, BI specialists, and Business Consultants to deliver value.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Staying abreast of the latest developments in data technology and actively sharing knowledge with colleagues.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monitoring the quality and stability of data solutions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mentoring and coaching other Analyticals Engineer.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do you have &lt;strong&gt;4 to 6 years&lt;/strong&gt; of experience, including at least &lt;strong&gt;2 years&lt;/strong&gt; in a cloud environment? Do you possess a passion for approaching projects from an end-to-end data perspective? We are delighted to receive your personal application and we’ll contact you for an interview and a (virtual) cup of coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can adeptly apply diverse data modeling styles and collaborate with our customers to develop the optimal data model for their needs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You grasp data structures &amp;amp; formats and are familiar with popular (cloud) data warehouses.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You navigate DBT with expertise, effortlessly crafting a new project, playing with all the DBT-blocks to build a castle from the ground up.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deep knowledge of SQL;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have a proven track record of effortlessly incorporating DevOps best practices such as CI/CD, IaC, and unit testing. CI/CD, which may sound like a secret code, is a realm you navigate with ease. You not only grasp its steps but can also articulate why it's indispensable for any data project. Moreover, you possess the skills to autonomously set it up.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You approach challenges with an analytical and solution-oriented mindset, and you're well-acquainted with agile methodologies and collaborative teamwork.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Docker and PySpark is a plus;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with dataframe API’s in Python (Panda’s, Polars, ...);&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fluent in Dutch and/or French and English.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your growth path&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Datashift is a firm believer in growing through its people. We will guide and support you providing many opportunities to develop and grow in the direction you want. However, we equally believe that it is you who takes ownership of your growth. That is why we give you the tools and the driving seat, it's up to you to do seize the opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One thing is for sure, surrounded by an entrepreneurial team, many opportunities will present themselves to deepen your expertise knowledge or broaden your Horizon in Data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this role, you are on the track to become a master in leading Data Engineering solutions for our clients. Whilst collaborating within Datashift on existing competence centers or helping to establish new practices. Making sure you and we keep up with the advancements in Data engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A highly entrepreneurial team;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A no-nonsense working environment with a focus on high quality;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent terms of employment (including company car, fuel card, meal vouchers &amp;amp; bonus);&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fringe benefits including continuous training that builds and extends professional, technical and management skills in all areas;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to grow together with Datashift in terms of capabilities as well as financial benefits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Oude Brusselsestraat 14, 2800 Mechelen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 9&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 51-200&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10485"/>
    <category term="Cloud"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term="Python"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10115</id>
    <title>Data Scientist Engineer  (Devoteam)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.362247+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Laurent  Huygens, Talent Acquisition Manager – Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Machelen (3 Culliganlaan 1831 Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 18/07/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you passionate about data-driven platforms, machine learning models, and innovative applications? As a Data Scientist/Engineer at Devoteam, you'll play a hands-on role in delivering impactful solutions across various clients and industries. Each mission we undertake has clear deliverables and deadlines, ensuring you gain diverse experience. For example, one month you might develop a predictive maintenance model, and the next, a customer segmentation model for a retail client.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Platform Setup:&lt;/strong&gt; Design and implement robust data platforms using Azure, AWS or Google Cloud and Databricks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Management:&lt;/strong&gt; Gather, prepare, and manage data for analysis.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Model Research:&lt;/strong&gt; Investigate and select appropriate machine learning models.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ML Modeling:&lt;/strong&gt; Develop and refine machine learning models.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Client Collaboration:&lt;/strong&gt; Spend approximately 50% of your time working directly with clients, either independently or as part of a team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build and maintain data platforms and pipelines using Azure, AWS or Google Cloud, Databricks, and Python.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop predictive and machine learning models tailored to client needs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advise clients on translating their business requirements into technical solutions using machine learning techniques.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stay updated on the latest trends in machine learning and AI, sharing insights with clients.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Act as a strategic partner to client Data Science teams, helping them navigate their challenges and aspirations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inspire clients with new data-driven opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bring best practices in Git, DevOps, and CICD to enhance client data platforms.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with Data Scientists, Data Engineers, and Business Stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Represent Devoteam both online and offline, showcasing our expertise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional Information:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why choose us?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cutting-edge Technology&lt;/strong&gt;: Embrace the latest advancements in IT and digital technologies as we constantly innovate to stay ahead of the competition. Our commitment to adopting state-of-the-art tools and methodologies ensures that you'll work on projects at the forefront of the industry.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Entrepreneur mindset&lt;/strong&gt;: We value our people over processes. You will develop and grow in an agile and ambitious company where it’s okay to take risks, make mistakes and change plans to find transformative solutions. At the same time, you will learn from the best, building relationships and skills that will last your entire career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Endless Learning Opportunities&lt;/strong&gt;: We value personal and professional growth. Through workshops, conferences, and certifications, we offer the resources needed to expand your skill set and reach new heights in your career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect with amazing people&lt;/strong&gt;: You will become part of a network of +10,000 Devoteamers spread over 20 countries.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborative Culture&lt;/strong&gt;: Teamwork is at the heart of our organisation. You'll be working side by side with a diverse group of IT experts who share your passion for excellence and will inspire you to think outside the box.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impactful Projects&lt;/strong&gt;: Tackle real-world challenges that matter! From revolutionising business processes to developing innovative solutions, you'll have the chance to make a genuine and positive impact on our clients and the community.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work-Life Balance&lt;/strong&gt;: We believe in a healthy work-life balance, ensuring that you have time to unwind, pursue your hobbies, and spend quality time with loved ones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inspiring and eco-friendly workplace&lt;/strong&gt;: We just moved to an amazing new building. We believe an inspiring workspace fuels creativity and fosters a positive work culture, allowing our employees to reach their full potential. The Wings building is also designed with eco-friendly features and energy-efficient systems. By reducing our ecological footprint, we are contributing to a greener future and aligning our business practices with our environmental values. The building is also very easily accessible by public transportation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive package&lt;/strong&gt;: We offer a competitive salary package with additional benefits like a company car, smartphone, medical insurance, pension plan, net allowance, laptop, meal vouchers, etc. We review our salary grid twice a year to ensure we are in line with the market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Devoteam, we combine strong values – respect, frankness, ambition, entrepreneurship &amp;amp; collaboration - with a fun environment that empowers you to innovate and succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan 3 , 1831 Machelen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 201-500&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10115"/>
    <category term="Artificial intelligence"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="Machine Learning"/>
    <category term="Python"/>
    <category term="Amazon Web Services (AWS)"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/12710</id>
    <title>Data Science and AI expert (Sopra Steria)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.362144+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Sopra Steria&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Frédéric La Roche, Recruiter – Sopra Steria Benelux SA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Brussels &amp;amp; Flanders (Culliganlaan 3b 1831 Machelen Belgium )&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 30/06/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you passionate about using data science and AI to real-world problems? At Sopra Steria, we’re looking for an experienced and versatile professional to help lead the design and delivery of advanced analytics and AI solutions across a wide range of domainssuch as public services, utilities, healthcare, mobility, and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this role, you will work on impactful projects from ideation to delivery. You’ll collaborate closely with both technical and business stakeholders transforming challenges into actionable insights and production-ready solutions. Whether it’s designing an optimization algorithm, building an LLM-based assistant, or delivering a forecasting pipeline, you’ll help clients unlock value from data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for someone who combines deep technical expertise with the maturity to take ownership, work autonomously, and guide teams and clients through the ever-evolving AI landscape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re seeking passionate colleagues who are eager to push the boundaries of digital transformation with AI. If you recognize yourself in most of the following, we’d love to talk:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have &lt;strong&gt;at least 5 years of experienc&lt;/strong&gt;e in delivering real-world AI and data science solutions in production environments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are proficient in &lt;strong&gt;Python &lt;/strong&gt;and comfortable with frameworks like scikit-learn, TensorFlow, PyTorch, or similar.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have practical experience with &lt;strong&gt;machine learning, and ideally exposure to domains like natural language processing, computer vision, predictive analytics, LLM’s &lt;/strong&gt;or&lt;strong&gt; optimization.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You’ve worked with &lt;strong&gt;at least one major cloud provider &lt;/strong&gt;(Azure, AWS, or GCP), and understand how to bring models into production securely and efficiently.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You understand how to balance model performance with business relevance, and how to translate analytical outcomes into &lt;strong&gt;actionable results&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You enjoy working in a team, guiding junior colleagues, and &lt;strong&gt;collaborating with clients&lt;/strong&gt; to define solution architectures and technical roadmaps.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You’re comfortable interacting with stakeholders and can &lt;strong&gt;communicate complex concepts &lt;/strong&gt;clearly and persuasively.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in &lt;strong&gt;project ownership&lt;/strong&gt;, technical leadership, or contributing to AI strategies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are fluent in &lt;strong&gt;English&lt;/strong&gt;, and speak either &lt;strong&gt;Dutch or French&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Can Offer You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A key role in one of Europe’s leading digital transformation companies, where innovation meets real-world impact.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to work on high-impact projects in AI and advanced analytics across industries and public institutions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A culture of collaboration and continuous learning, supported by an expert network of consultants, architects, and engineers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Access to our Sopra Steria Academy, with a wide range of training opportunities and certifications.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A hybrid and flexible working model, with access to offices across Belgium.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Career development opportunities both locally and internationally, within a growing Data &amp;amp; AI practice.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our employees are known for making bold choices and delivering results. Work among high-level professionals at the forefront of corporate software solutions and innovation at Europe’s Leading Digital Service Provider.  &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We offer a generous employee benefits package that includes:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A variety of perks, such as mobility options (including a company car), insurance coverage, meal vouchers, eco-cheques, and more.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continuous learning opportunities through the Sopra Steria Academy to support your career development.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to connect with fellow Sopra Steria colleagues at various team events. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;People are the cornerstone of our success. That’s why we aspire to be bolder together. Our goal is to build high-functioning teams and healthy team environments that inspire and help each other to deliver excellence for each of our customers.  &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excited about this job opportunity? Ready to shape the world with us? Great! We are looking forward to your application! &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At&amp;nbsp;OptimAI, we combine the best of both worlds:&amp;nbsp;data science&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;supply chain optimization. You will be part of a forward-thinking team where you can shape the future of data science and supply chain management. This is an excellent opportunity to make a real difference and grow your career in a field that is rapidly evolving and in high demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you thrive on challenge, continuous learning, and want to make an impact in a fast-growing field, apply now to join the&amp;nbsp;OptimAI Team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;______&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sopra Steria is an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will be considered for employment without regard to age, ancestry, nationality, color, family or medical leave, gender identity or expression, genetic information, immigration status, marital status, medical condition, national origin, physical or mental disability, political affiliation, protected veteran or military status, race, ethnicity, religion, gender (including pregnancy), sexual orientation or any other characteristic protected by applicable local laws, regulations and ordinances. We foster a work environment that is inclusive and respectful of all differences.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 48&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 501-1000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/12710"/>
    <category term="Python"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10562</id>
    <title>Senior Azure BI &amp; Data Engineer (Datashift)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.362035+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Datashift&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Fred Thiebaut, Recruiter – Datashift&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Mechelen (Oude Brusselsestraat 14, 2800 Mechelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on 28/08/2025, last change 28/08/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Datashift is a fast-growing consultancy team with a focus on delivering solutions that answer business questions with data and facts. For one of our fastest growing practices, we are looking for a skilled &lt;strong&gt;Azure BI &amp;amp; Data Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do you have at least&lt;strong&gt; 4 to 6 years of experience?&lt;/strong&gt; Do you love to work on projects and look at them from an end-to-end data perspective. Then we are delighted to receive your personal application and we’ll contact you for an interview and a (virtual) cup of coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leverage your Azure expertise to credibly translate customer needs into components and best practices within the Azure Data Platform.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Serve as the primary internal and external contact for specialized Azure expertise, with the opportunity to progress toward an Architect role.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design and build data solutions within the Azure framework, making the trade-off between cost and maintainability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You thrive on collaborating with colleagues and leverage your expertise to maximize your impact within our organization.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay up to date with technical developments, particularly those related to Azure, and quickly identify new features that can add value to data solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have 4+ years of hands-on experience in the Microsoft BI ecosystem (Azure Data Factory, Azure Synapse Analytics, Databricks, Microsoft Fabric, Analysis Services en SQL Server Integration Services), preferably within an Azure cloud environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in building and optimizing ETL/ELT data pipelines and integrating data from diverse sources (also api’s).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of modern data architecture concepts, including Data Warehouses, the Kimball methodology, and Data Lakehouses, with hands-on experience and best practices in these areas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;SQL is your Swiss army knife for data transformation, and you’re also well-versed in Python to tackle any data challenge that comes your way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A highly entrepreneurial team;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A no-nonsense working environment with a focus on high quality;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent terms of employment (including company car, fuel card, meal vouchers &amp;amp; bonus);&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fringe benefits including continuous training that builds and extends professional, technical and management skills in all areas;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to grow together with Datashift in terms of capabilities as well as financial benefits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Oude Brusselsestraat 14, 2800 Mechelen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 9&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 51-200&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10562"/>
    <category term="Cloud"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="ETL / Datawarehouse"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/11482</id>
    <title>Data Engineer (CLOVR)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.361923+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: CLOVR&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Wout Raeyen, Managing Partner - Senior Recruiter – CLOVR&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Goetsenhoven (3300, Goetsenhoven )&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 20/03/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Voor deze gerenommeerde internationale onderneming te Tienen zijn we op zoek naar een gedreven Full Stack IT Data Engineer&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jouw takenpakket bestaat uit onder andere:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ontwerpen, ontwikkelen en onderhouden van data architectuur en pipelines&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zorgen voor een efficiënte dataflow over verschillende systemen ter ondersteuning van collega's zoals data scientists, data analisten, business analisten etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Automatiseren van data-input, transformatie en opslag workflows&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Data processing/orchestration (via Apache Spark &amp;amp; Airflow)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zorgen voor een uitstekende datakwaliteit standaard opdat alle data accuraat en compleet beschikbaar is&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monitoring en optimalisatie&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;....&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wie ben jij?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je hebt minstens 2-3 jaar ervaring als Data Engineer (of een gelijkaardige relevante rol) en beschikt over goede communicatieve en analytische vaardigheden;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uitstekende kennis van SQL Server, Oracle, Postgress, MongoDB, ETL, Cloud data platform (Azure), Airflow,... én een sterke kennis van programmeertalen zoals Python, R, SQL,..&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je kan moeilijke technische concepten duidelijk en eenvoudig overbrengen naar niet-technische gebruikers&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wat is het aanbod?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Contract onbepaalde duur in een groeiende internationale speler&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Salaris afhankelijk van jouw competenties (tot ongeveer 4900 euro bruto/maand)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vergoeding woonwerkverkeer&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maaltijd- en ecocheques&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Netto-onkostenvergoeding&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uitgebreide hospitalisatieverzekering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Zeer interessante groepsverzekering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Glijdende uren &amp;amp; mogelijkheid tot thuiswerk (2 dagen/week)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;GSM en laptop&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;39 u/week maar wél 12 ADV dagen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;...&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Lil &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 108&lt;/li&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/11482"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="ETL / Datawarehouse"/>
    <category term="Oracle"/>
    <category term="Python"/>
    <category term="Apache HTTP Server"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10398</id>
    <title>Data Engineer ( AWS, Azure or GCP) (Devoteam)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.361806+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Laurent  Huygens, Talent Acquisition Manager – Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Machelen (3 Cullinganlaan 1831 Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on 22/08/2025, last change 22/08/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a &lt;strong&gt;Data Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;, you will build and share knowledge with your colleagues. With initiatives like our knowledge sharing sessions, you have various chances to bond and exchange ideas with colleagues, and keep up to date with the latest developments in the field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You love working with data and are familiar with multiple data platforms and enjoy developing spark applications. You will work in a multidisciplinary team, including data scientists, data architects, analysts, ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are&amp;nbsp;a &lt;strong&gt;Data Engineer &lt;/strong&gt;and &lt;strong&gt;fascinated by Data &lt;/strong&gt;and can bring :&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A good knowledge on one or multiple programming languages: Scala, Python...&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A good knowledge on one or multiple technologies:&amp;nbsp; Spark, Kafka, Nifi...&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working on one or multiple Cloud Data platforms (Databricks, Azure, AWS, Google, Cloudera)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fluency in Dutch or French (one of these languages is mandatory) and English&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why choose us?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cutting-edge Technology&lt;/strong&gt;: Embrace the latest advancements in IT and digital technologies as we constantly innovate to stay ahead of the competition. Our commitment to adopting state-of-the-art tools and methodologies ensures that you'll work on projects at the forefront of the industry.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Entrepreneur mindset&lt;/strong&gt;: We value our people over processes. You will develop and grow in an agile and ambitious company where it’s okay to take risks, make mistakes and change plans to find transformative solutions. At the same time, you will learn from the best, building relationships and skills that will last your entire career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Endless Learning Opportunities&lt;/strong&gt;: We value personal and professional growth. Through workshops, conferences, and certifications, we offer the resources needed to expand your skill set and reach new heights in your career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect with amazing people&lt;/strong&gt;: You will become part of a network of +10,000 Devoteamers spread over 20 countries.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborative Culture&lt;/strong&gt;: Teamwork is at the heart of our organisation. You'll be working side by side with a diverse group of IT experts who share your passion for excellence and will inspire you to think outside the box.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impactful Projects&lt;/strong&gt;: Tackle real-world challenges that matter! From revolutionising business processes to developing innovative solutions, you'll have the chance to make a genuine and positive impact on our clients and the community.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work-Life Balance&lt;/strong&gt;: We believe in a healthy work-life balance, ensuring that you have time to unwind, pursue your hobbies, and spend quality time with loved ones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inspiring and eco-friendly workplace&lt;/strong&gt;: We just moved to an amazing new building. We believe an inspiring workspace fuels creativity and fosters a positive work culture, allowing our employees to reach their full potential. The Wings building is also designed with eco-friendly features and energy-efficient systems. By reducing our ecological footprint, we are contributing to a greener future and aligning our business practices with our environmental values. The building is also very easily accessible by public transportation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive package&lt;/strong&gt;: We offer a competitive salary package with additional benefits like a company car, smartphone, medical insurance, pension plan, net allowance, laptop, meal vouchers, etc. We review our salary grid twice a year to ensure we are in line with the market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Devoteam, we combine strong values – respect, frankness, ambition, entrepreneurship &amp;amp; collaboration - with a fun environment that empowers you to innovate and succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan 3 , 1831 Machelen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 201-500&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10398"/>
    <category term="Cloud"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="Big data management"/>
    <category term="ETL / Datawarehouse"/>
    <category term="Machine Learning"/>
    <category term="Amazon Web Services (AWS)"/>
    <category term="Docker"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/12370</id>
    <title>Senior Data Engineer (Xylos)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.361683+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Xylos&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Elke Meuleman, Recruiter – Xylos&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Vlaanderen en Brussel (Vlaanderen en Brussel)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 25/04/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;YOUR DAILY ADVENTURE &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Als Senior Data Engineer maak je deel uit van een divers en hoogopgeleid team van consultants. Jij neemt de leiding in uitdagende en impactvolle data-projecten.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dit ga je doen:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je leidt het ontwerp en de implementatie van schaalbare, high-performance dataplatformen, afgestemd op de behoeften van de klant.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je bent de trusted advisor voor klanten, waarbij je advies biedt over de nieuwste Azure-oplossingen, best practices en trends.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je begeleidt de volledige levenscyclus van data-engineeringprojecten—van het verzamelen van vereisten tot implementatie en optimalisatie.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je ontwerpt, implementeert en beheert geavanceerde ETL/ELT-pipelines om data te extraheren, te transformeren en te integreren vanuit diverse bronsystemen naar centrale data warehouses.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je ontwerpt en optimaliseert datamodellen voor analytische en operationele toepassingen.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je configureert en optimaliseert Azure Data Services voor robuuste prestaties en beveiliging.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je werkt nauw samen met stakeholders uit zowel de business als technische domeinen om datastrategieën af te stemmen op hun doelstellingen.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je bent eenmentor en coach voor onze junior engineers en je stimuleert groei binnen het team.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je deelt jouw expertise door interne kennissessies te leiden en bij te dragen aan technische excellentie binnen de organisatie.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Je houdt je kennis up-to-date door trainingen te volgen en seminars bij te wonen, zodat onze oplossingen altijd gebruikmaken van de nieuwste innovaties.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;THE BEST VERSION OF YOU &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data, hét nieuwe goud! Binnen onze missie om mensen en organisaties digitaal fit en veilig te houden speelt Data een heel belangrijke rol, dat is een open deur, dat weet jij ook! Wij ontwikkelen voor onze klanten moderne dataplatformen. Om deze groei verder te blijven ondersteunen zoeken we een nieuwe collega, een Senior Data Engineer, eentje mét &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;a href="https://xylos.com/about-us/"&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DRIVE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt; en veel #Goesting.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Knik je “Ja” bij het volgende? Dan moeten we kennismaken:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uitgebreide ervaring met het Microsoft Azure Data Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gevorderde kennis van Azure Data Lake, Data Warehouses, Azure Data Factory, Databricks, Synapse Analytics, en verwante tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ervaren met SQL, NoSQL, en het ontwerpen van schaalbare, high-performance architecturen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ervaring met Microsoft Fabric is een pluspunt&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sterke programmeervaardigheden in Python, met een focus op Pandas en Apache Spark&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een bewezen vermogen om complexe problemen op te lossen met creatieve en robuuste oplossingen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uitmuntende analytische skills en een proactieve mindset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een communicatieve teamspeler die helder en effectief samenwerkt met klanten en collega's&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Nauwkeurigheid en oog voor detail, met een track record van hoogwaardige oplossingen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Voortdurend leren zit in jouw DNA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vloeiend in Nederlands en Engels; Frans is een plus&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Masterdiploma Computerwetenschappen, Wiskunde, Burgerlijk Ingenieur, Industrieel Ingenieur of minstens 8 jaar ervaring in Data Engineering rollen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Er zit meer in een Xylos-job dan je denkt&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een écht moderne werkplek. Dat betekent ook een warme, menselijke werksfeer waar jouw dagelijkse beleving centraal staat…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Uitdagende projecten met het beste dat technologie te bieden heeft en een groeiplan op maat van jou en je loopbaanambities…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een aantrekkelijk salaris aangevuld met een resem voordelen: dag-, thuis-, internetvergoeding, groeps- en hospitalisatieverzekering, bedrijfswagen…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We bieden ook een atypisch bonuspakket. Dat kan je netto cashen én spenderen aan multimedia, of zelfs gewoon extra verlofdagen…&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Maak alvast kennis met de atypische &lt;strong&gt;Xylos-vibe&lt;/strong&gt; op Instagram &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/xylos_belgium/"&gt;https://www.instagram.com/xylos_belgium/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Noorderlaan 139, 2030 ANTWERPEN&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 4&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 51-200&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/12370"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="Python"/>
    <category term="NoSQL / MongoDB"/>
    <category term="Databricks"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10595</id>
    <title>Data Platform Engineer (Madison Recruitment)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.361533+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Madison Recruitment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Piet Leemans, Markering Strategist &amp;amp; Process Analyst – Madison IT &amp;amp; Engineering Recruitment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Antwerpen (Antwerpen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 20/03/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Onze klant is een&lt;strong&gt; internationale speler&lt;/strong&gt; en met 50 000 werknemers opzoek naar nieuw talent om hun team te versterken. Er heerst een sterke familie-sfeer met respect voor elk individu en ze streven naar sterke diversiteit. Ook investeren ze in het milieu maar vooral ook in hun eigen mensen. &lt;strong&gt;Work-life balance&lt;/strong&gt; staat hier centraal waardoor je zelf jou agenda planning opmaakt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Voor hun ben ik opzoek naar een Data Platform Engineer om hun data- en analytics platformteam te versterken. In deze rol speel je een cruciale rol bij het ontwikkelen, onderhouden en optimaliseren van hun data platform.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Takenpakket:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ontwerpen, implementeren en beheren van de infrastructuur en services van hun data platform op Databricks en Azure.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Samenwerken met data engineers, data scientists en andere stakeholders&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bijdragen aan architectuur- en ontwerpbeslissingen van het platform, met een focus op data mesh principes&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Profiel&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een masterdiploma in Computerwetenschappen, Informatietechnologie, Engineering of een gerelateerd vakgebied.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;2-3 jaar werkervaring achter de rug&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sterke expertise in Azure en Databricks, inclusief infrastructuur als code, data lake storage en ETL-processen.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ervaring in platform engineering binnen een data- en analytics-context.&lt;br&gt;Bekendheid met data mesh principes en ervaring met implementatie hiervan.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Maar bovenal zijn ze op zoek naar iemand met goede analytische vaardigheden, affiniteit met IoT, die graag samenwerkt in open communicatie en leergierig is.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Aanbod&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Competitief salaris&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Groepsverzekering, hospitalisatieverzekering en extralegale voordelen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Flexibele werkuren&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;20 vakantiedagen en 12 ADV-dagen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een bedrijfswagen via cafetariaplan, laptop en GSM&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bijkomende opleidingsmogelijkheden&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Goede work-life balance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Frankrijklei&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 174&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 11 - 50&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Staffing &amp;amp; Recruiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10595"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/13525</id>
    <title>Lead Data Architect (Visser &amp; Van Baars)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.361423+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Visser &amp;amp; Van Baars&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Vladimir Vets, Business Manager – Vibe Group Belgium&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Machelen (Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on 27/08/2025, last change 27/08/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location: Machelen (Culliganlaan 3)&lt;br&gt;Contract: Full-time - Permanent&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;About the company&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;For one of our clients, we are looking for a &lt;strong&gt;Lead Data Architect / Crew Manager&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;br&gt;This organization is at the forefront of &lt;strong&gt;cloud, data and AI innovation&lt;/strong&gt;, with a strong international presence and a clear vision to use technology as a driver of growth and transformation. They work with modern cloud platforms and partner with key players such as &lt;strong&gt;Google Cloud, Microsoft and AWS&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Your role&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a &lt;strong&gt;Google Data Architect&lt;/strong&gt;, you will help the client design strategies, roadmaps, and scalable data architectures that enable business growth and innovation. You will bring structure to global enterprises, support scale-ups in leveraging data for rapid growth, and show traditional companies the possibilities of cloud-based data solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Architecture here goes beyond diagrams - it's about &lt;strong&gt;building practical, scalable solutions&lt;/strong&gt;. That's why the team invests in training and coaching, making sure every architect understands both the code and the impact of architectural decisions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition to your client-facing responsibilities, you will also take on the role of &lt;strong&gt;Crew Manager&lt;/strong&gt;. You'll coach and guide a team of consultants, shape the vision of the department, and foster innovation and continuous learning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What we're looking for&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English; Dutch is a strong plus. French is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Master's degree in Computer Science or equivalent by experience.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;At least 3 years of experience with &lt;strong&gt;Data Modelling, Data Transformations and Data Governance&lt;/strong&gt; on a cloud platform.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Experience with Google Cloud&lt;/strong&gt; (BigQuery, Looker, Cloud Storage, Dataform) is a plus.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Background in Azure or AWS?&lt;/strong&gt; The client provides full support and training to help you smoothly transition to &lt;strong&gt;Google Cloud Platform (GCP)&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of tools such as dbt, Airbyte or Power BI.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Strong communication and interpersonal skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Entrepreneurial mindset: curious, hands-on, and not afraid to try new things.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ability to collaborate with stakeholders at all levels and design scalable solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3&gt;What's in it for you&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Work on impactful Cloud, Data &amp;amp; AI projects with a forward-thinking organization&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dynamic and entrepreneurial environment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Clear career growth path supported by certifications, training &amp;amp; learning platforms&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Support in transitioning from &lt;strong&gt;Azure/AWS to GCP&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inspiring, sustainable workplace with healthy work-life balance&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Competitive salary package&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Graanmarkt, 2, 2000 Antwerpen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 51-200&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Staffing &amp;amp; Recruiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/13525"/>
    <category term="Cloud"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/11231</id>
    <title>Data Architect (Madison Recruitment)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.361307+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Madison Recruitment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Piet Leemans, Markering Strategist &amp;amp; Process Analyst – Madison IT &amp;amp; Engineering Recruitment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Antwerpen (None)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 20/03/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Voor onze klant in Antwerpen zijn wij op zoek naar een &lt;strong&gt;Data Architect.&lt;/strong&gt; Het bedrijf maakt deel uit van een internationale HR-groep en is een toonaangevende speler in België. Met ruim 2400 werknemers bekleden ze in België de tweede positie binnen hun niche. Als HR dienstverlener bieden ze verschillende vormen van flexibele arbeid en uiteenlopende diensten aan. Het hoofdkantoor in Antwerpen biedt support op gebieden zoals IT, legal, finance en payroll, zodat elk merk zich kan focussen op de kernactiviteiten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Omdat ze momenteel in volle groei zijn, zoeken ze een Data Architect om hun team te versterken. Als Data Architect kom je in hun data team terecht.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Als Data Architect ben je verantwoordelijk voor het ontwerpen van de datasystemen en datasets. Hierbij werk je mee de toekomstgerichte &lt;strong&gt;datastrategie en -architectuur&lt;/strong&gt; en houdt rekening met innovaties binnen data, AI en reporting. Daarnaast fungeer je als brug tussen analisten en engineers, communiceer je met stakeholders, en ontwerp je oplossingen voor dataplatformuitbreidingen, datastromen en cloudintegraties. Innovatie en ondersteuning spelen hierbij een sleutelrol.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Dit doe je binnen een organisatie waar je zelf veel kan ondernemen.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Profiel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Je hebt minimum drie jaar ervaring in een soortgelijke functie.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;goede kennis van data management &amp;amp; architectuur concepten (data&lt;br&gt;warehousing, data lakehouse, data mesh, data governance, ...).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;kennis van SQL en basiservaring met Python &amp;amp; GIT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Bachelor of Masterdiploma&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Vloeiend in de Nederlandse en Engelse taal&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Aanbod&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Hierbij krijg je een &lt;strong&gt;ruim salarispakket &lt;/strong&gt;aangeboden en kan je &lt;strong&gt;flexibel van thuis uit werken.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;50% thuiswerk mogelijk en flexibele uren&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Vast contract in een stabiele omgeving&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Uitgebreid verloningspakket (incl. Bedrijfswagen of mobiliteitsbudget, maaltijdcheques, verzekeringen, nettovergoedingen, bonussen, etc.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Uitdagende positie waar je het verschil zal kunnen maken&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;Werken in een omgeving met groeimogelijkheden&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p dir="ltr"&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interesse?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;Stuur dan je CV via Editx&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Frankrijklei&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 174&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 11 - 50&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Staffing &amp;amp; Recruiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/11231"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term="Python"/>
    <category term="VCS - GIT"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/4795</id>
    <title>Cloud Data Engineer (Capgemini Belgium)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.361183+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Capgemini Belgium&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Frankie Smagghe, Sr. IT Recruiter – Capgemini Belgium NV/SA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Machelen (Hybrid work location (home, client site, Capgemini office), work up to 70% from home)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 20/03/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;As Stephen Few states: “We are overwhelmed by information, not because there is too much, but because we haven't learned how to tame it.” Capgemini Insights &amp;amp; Data is looking for people who tame data in such a way that the most complex data can be easily interpreted.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will join a group of data enthusiasts within a global organization of 350.000 employees. As our growth potential within Belgium is huge, you will vastly grow with us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you believe that honesty, boldness, modesty, trust, freedom, team spirit and fun are important company values, then we have a match. Check it out,&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.capgemini.com/about-us/who-we-are/values-and-ethics/"&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;you find our seven core values. Combined with firm goals on equality, inclusion and zero carbon emissions, Capgemini will be your partner to get the future you want.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We are looking for a&amp;nbsp;&lt;strong&gt;Cloud Data Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;&amp;nbsp;to help our clients in their digital transformations.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What will you do?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Integrate, transform and consolidate data from various structured and unstructured data systems&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure data pipelines and data stores are high-performing, efficient, organized, and reliable, given a set of business requirements and constraints&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Create and design data models&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Translate functional requirements into a technical design&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Provide and maintain technical documentation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You have knowledge of / You are keen to learn more about&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Azure Data Factory, Azure SQL database and Databricks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Azure DevOps for Deployment&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Azure Analysis Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Data Modeling methodologies (Kimball, Data Vault)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SQL and T-SQL&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Similar knowledge in the AWS and/or GCP cloud technology stack will be highly appreciated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Relevant Certificates&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;DP-900: Microsoft Azure Data Fundamentals&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;DP-203: Data Engineering on Microsoft Azure&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Any certificate on Databricks&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Continuous Learning&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Capgemini Belgium is a&amp;nbsp;&lt;a href="https://www.top-employers.com/en/certified-top-employers-search/?id=1241"&gt;Top Employer&lt;/a&gt;&amp;nbsp;for the 18th year in a row. Opportunities to learn are an important aspect of this Top Employer status. The two most important criteria to apply is to have an appetite for data and a willingness to continuously learn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Location Belgium&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part-time on-site, part-time home working.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Communication and personality&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;English: must have.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;French and/or Dutch: nice to have.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good written and oral communication, problem-solving mindset, able to work independently, dynamic.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good presentation skills.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ability to work in a team, integrate and work in an international/multi-cultural environment, on variable-sized projects.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Bessenveldstraat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 501-1000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/4795"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="Database"/>
    <category term="Amazon Web Services (AWS)"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/9028</id>
    <title>Azure Data Architect - Data &amp; AI  (Cegeka)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.361038+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Cegeka&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Anneleen V., Talent Acquisition Partner – Cegeka&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Gent – Brussel – Antwerpen (Gent – Brussel – Antwerpen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 20/03/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dé missie binnen onze Data Solutions Unit?&amp;nbsp;Moderne dataplatformen van de toekomst in te richten met de laatste technologieën in Azure cloud. Draag jij hier je steentje aan bij als ervaren Azure Data Architect?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;In je rol als Azure Data Architect werk je nauw samen met ervaren collega’s aan het opmaken van Data Platformen in de Microsoft Azure Cloud. (Data Platformen, Big Data, Advanced Analytics en AI)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je vindt een complexe Business &amp;amp; IT omgeving een uitdaging. Als architect bepaal je samen met de klant de architectuur van het toekomstig Data Platform en ben je hiervoor eindverantwoordelijke.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je bent in staat om onze klanten optimaal gebruik te laten maken van de ongekende mogelijkheden van het Azure Cloud Platform. Jouw overtuigingskracht en passie komen hierbij goed van pas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je gaat het gesprek aan met zowel technische mensen als mensen van de business.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je bent gestructureerd en analytisch, kan eenvoudig abstractie maken en beschikt over een probleemoplossende geest.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Door jouw coachende stijl weet je andere projectleden naar een hoger niveau tillen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wat breng jij mee?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je hebt een aanstekelijk enthousiasme over data &amp;amp; cloud services.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je hebt als data architect ervaring in enkele of alle Microsoft Azure Data Services (Data Lake, Data Factory, Azure Databricks, Azure SQL Server, Azure Synapse, Azure Data Explorer, Azure DevOps, …)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je brengt een flexibele, zelfstandige en collegiale houding met je mee.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Goede communicatieve vaardigheden, klantgerichtheid en nauwkeurigheid zijn tevens zeer belangrijk in deze rol.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Onze projecten vinden voornamelijk plaats in de regio Gent – Brussel – Antwerpen. Als je aanwezigheid bij de klant niet vereist is dan kan je in het Cegeka kantoor dichtst bij je woonplaats werken (Antwerpen, Hasselt of Gent), waarbij hybride werken ook mogelijk is.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wat hebben wij jou te bieden?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;We vragen heel wat (talenten) van jou. Gelukkig krijg je er ook heel wat voor terug! Een krak zoals jij verdient immers het allerbeste!&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Competenties en karakter zijn voor ons essentieel, naast ervaring en ambities. Cegeka investeert voortdurend in talent management opdat elke medewerker zijn potentieel kan realiseren.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Innovatie en kennisdeling staan bij ons hoog op de agenda. We zijn altijd op zoek naar vernieuwing en verbetering bij onze klanten. Je krijgt volop kansen om hierin actief deel te nemen.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je komt terecht in een hecht, gedreven en gepassioneerd team waarin het aangenaam én leuk werken is. We hebben zelfs een eigen Data Solutions fun team.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Begeleiding op maat! Jij geeft aan waar je interesses liggen. We bieden verschillende carrièrepaden aan, en kijken samen hoe we je verder kunnen helpen ontplooien.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Naast het competitief brutosalaris, een (elektrische) bedrijfswagen of mobiliteitsbudget, maaltijdcheques, ecocheques groeps-en hospitalisatieverzekering, gsm-abonnement, forfaitaire onkostenvergoeding en krachtige laptop, bieden we jou flexibele werkuren en een mooie work/life balans.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Dankzij ons Flex Reward Plan kunnen we een verloning op maat aanbieden.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We hechten we waarde aan duurzaamheid door CO2-neutraliteit na te streven met de elektrificatie van ons wagenpark en een milieuvriendelijk datacenter. We ontwikkelen innovatieve oplossingen met een positieve impact op milieu, mens en maatschappij, en streven naar een inclusieve en diverse werkomgeving waarin iedereen gewaardeerd en gehoord wordt.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Kempische Steenweg &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 20&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 5001-10000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Computer &amp;amp; Network Security&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/9028"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/13463</id>
    <title>Azure Data Engineer (Visser &amp; Van Baars)</title>
    <updated>2025-08-31T06:19:24.333201+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Visser &amp;amp; Van Baars&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Vladimir Vets, Business Manager – Vibe Group Belgium&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Vlaams-Brabant (Vlaams-Brabant)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on 22/08/2025, last change 22/08/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ben jij een Data Engineer met een passie voor cloud-native technologieën? Bouw jij graag schaalbare en betrouwbare data-oplossingen in Azure? Dan zijn wij op zoek naar jou!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Jouw rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Als Data Engineer ben je verantwoordelijk voor het ontwerpen, ontwikkelen en onderhouden van een moderne enterprise Data Platform. Je werkt in agile DevOps-teams en schakelt met verschillende stakeholders om hoogwaardige, veilige en efficiënte dataoplossingen te realiseren.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Jouw verantwoordelijkheden&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Platform Development&lt;/strong&gt;: Ontwerpen, implementeren en optimaliseren van data-opslag en verwerkingsoplossingen (Azure Data Lake, Data Factory, SQL, Databricks, Microsoft Fabric).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Integratie &amp;amp; ETL/ELT&lt;/strong&gt;: Bouwen van robuuste pipelines en modelleren van data voor analytisch gebruik (Power BI, SQL).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Monitoring &amp;amp; Support&lt;/strong&gt;: Beheren, monitoren en verbeteren van performance en betrouwbaarheid.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DevOps &amp;amp; CI/CD&lt;/strong&gt;: Integratie van dataoplossingen binnen agile teams via Azure DevOps of GitHub Actions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Stakeholder samenwerking&lt;/strong&gt;: Nauw samenwerken met Data Owners, BI-analisten, Architecten en Governance Leads.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Workflow Automation&lt;/strong&gt;: Automatiseren van processen met Python (PySpark), PowerShell of Logic Apps.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Governance &amp;amp; Quality&lt;/strong&gt;: Toepassen van best practices op het gebied van security, governance en datakwaliteit.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Documentatie &amp;amp; Standards&lt;/strong&gt;: Bijhouden van duidelijke documentatie en werken volgens enterprise-standaarden.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelor of Master in Computer Science, Data Engineering of gelijkaardig.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Minimaal 3 jaar ervaring als Data Engineer, bij voorkeur met Azure.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sterke kennis van Azure tools (Data Factory, Synapse, Databricks, SQL).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ervaring met DevOps en CI/CD.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Kennis van data governance, security en datakwaliteit.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ervaring met rapportagetools (Power BI, Qlik, Tableau) is een plus.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Uitstekende kennis van het Nederlands is een must.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Ons aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een innovatieve en dynamische werkomgeving.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ruimte voor eigenaarschap, groei en innovatie.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Hybride werkmodel met flexibiliteit.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Competitief salaris met uitgebreide voordelen.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Toegang tot trainingen, certificeringen en doorgroeimogelijkheden in Azure &amp;amp; data engineering.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Graanmarkt, 2, 2000 Antwerpen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 10&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 51-200&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Staffing &amp;amp; Recruiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/13463"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
  </entry>
</feed>
