<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>d34c4e59-e6f2-4fce-8ea6-e0da265fbf22</id>
  <title>editx</title>
  <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.350912+00:00</updated>
  <link href="https://www.editx.eu" rel="alternate"/>
  <generator uri="https://lkiesow.github.io/python-feedgen" version="1.0.0">python-feedgen</generator>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/14674</id>
    <title>Master IT – Industrial Software (TalentChain)</title>
    <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.373468+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: TalentChain&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Benjamin De Pooter, Oprichter / Senior Recruiter – TalentChain&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Lokeren (Lokeren)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 21/11/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Beschrijving&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Onze klant in de regio Lokeren is een gevestigde waarde binnen geautomatiseerde industriële systemen en digitalisering. Ze ondersteunen productiebedrijven bij het optimaliseren en toekomstbestendig maken van hun processen. In een innovatieve, hoogtechnologische omgeving werken ze aan oplossingen die efficiëntie verhogen, kwaliteit bewaken en operators ondersteunen. Het team combineert technisch vakmanschap met een pragmatische KMO-geest, waarin korte beslissingslijnen en ondernemerschap centraal staan.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Als IT-ontwikkelaar binnen het Industrial IT-team werk je aan de ontwikkeling en optimalisatie van industriële softwaretoepassingen zoals receptuursystemen, dashboards en MES-oplossingen. Je analyseert klantbehoeften, vertaalt deze naar robuuste software en zorgt voor een vlotte integratie met zowel IT- als OT-omgevingen. Je werkt nauw samen met automation engineers, productiemanagers en andere stakeholders om ervoor te zorgen dat de oplossing technisch sterk, performant en gebruiksvriendelijk is. Dankzij jouw analytische aanpak, leergierigheid en focus op security draag je mee bij aan toepassingen die processen veiliger, efficiënter en aangenamer maken voor alle betrokkenen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Profiel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Masterdiploma in ingenieurswetenschappen.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sterke technische kennis van softwareontwikkeling (.NET, C#, Python, SQL, cloudplatformen, API-integraties).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analytisch, probleemoplossend en aandacht voor performantie en security.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leergierig en gemotiveerd om te groeien binnen industriële IT.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pluspunt: ervaring met OT-integraties en protocollen (OPC UA, MQTT, Modbus, ProfiNet).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Aanbod&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een fulltime rol binnen een groeiende organisatie met sterke technische expertise.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een aantrekkelijk en volledig salarispakket.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Flexibele werktijden en een toegankelijke, betrokken teamomgeving.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een cultuur waarin kennisdeling, opleiding en persoonlijke ontwikkeling centraal staan.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Regelmatige teamactiviteiten, inspiratiesessies en een gezond evenwicht tussen werk en welzijn.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Katerstraat &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 5&lt;/li&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/14674"/>
    <category term="Cloud"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term=".NET"/>
    <category term="APIs"/>
    <category term="C#"/>
    <category term="Python"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10402</id>
    <title>M365 Platform &amp; Security Architect (Devoteam)</title>
    <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.373362+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Laurent  Huygens, Talent Acquisition Manager – Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Machelen (3 Cullinganlaan 1831 Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 12/11/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like these keywords, you’ll love this role:&lt;br&gt;#M365 #Entra #Defender #Purview #Intune&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s more fundamental in IT these days than a Digital Workplace that is fully secured and compliant by end users?&lt;br&gt;Develop, design, and build the future with us as a Microsoft 365 Workplace Security Architect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a Workplace Security Architect, you know the solutions that can help in increasing the workplace security maturity. You know what Zero-trust is and how you can use Microsoft technology to protect customers against cyberthreats. You will work with Client’s Business &amp;amp; Technical employees to capture, discuss, create, build, deliver &amp;amp; verify solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this position, we’re looking for &lt;strong&gt;all seniority levels&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have a broad view of the Modern Workplace building blocks, from classic solutions to Microsoft 365.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have a broad view of all the Microsoft 365 Defender Solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have expertise on how to secure Endpoints, Identities, Apps and Data with Microsoft 365 Defender, Intune, Entra and Purview.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You can design an entire architecture that protects the corporate data and prevent data loss.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You are an expert in one or more Microsoft (365) solutions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise with Defender for Cloud and/or Microsoft Sentinel.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have experience and/or a talent to deliver results-driven workshops with the customer to capture requirements, explain the new way of working that can be realized with out-of-the-box M365, and the benefits that can be realized.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise or affinity with the Microsoft Power low-code Platform or Ometa to further automate and increase productivity in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You’re ready to drive change and bring creative tech ideas to life.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You’re either proficient in Dutch or French (or you want to learn) and fluent in English.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Bonus-points] MS certified (or willing to obtain). Certifications in scope: SC-100, SC-300, SC-400, MS-102, MS-203 etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you do not feel fully confident that you meet the requirements above, please don’t worry. Just apply. Together we’ll discover what you can bring to the table, in which role you would fit best and how you could potentially grow at Devoteam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our promises to you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;As a digital native you will have a positive impact at top organizations in Belgium.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Direct access to the Microsoft organization and programs thanks to our global partnership.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prepare to inspire and be inspired by other Devoteamers in tech communities.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We enable local and international collaboration and exchange with other tech leaders and specialists, knowledge sharing, peer-to-peer coaching.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A personalized career plan with training offers in soft- &amp;amp; hard skills and certifications aligned to your needs &amp;amp; expertise.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our servant leadership supports opportunities to grow your personal brand through blogs, keynote sessions, and more.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;#techies in our minds, #creatives in our hearts, #change in our DNA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why choose us?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cutting-edge Technology&lt;/strong&gt;: Embrace the latest advancements in IT and digital technologies as we constantly innovate to stay ahead of the competition. Our commitment to adopting state-of-the-art tools and methodologies ensures that you'll work on projects at the forefront of the industry.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Entrepreneur mindset&lt;/strong&gt;: We value our people over processes. You will develop and grow in an agile and ambitious company where it’s okay to take risks, make mistakes and change plans to find transformative solutions. At the same time, you will learn from the best, building relationships and skills that will last your entire career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Endless Learning Opportunities&lt;/strong&gt;: We value personal and professional growth. Through workshops, conferences, and certifications, we offer the resources needed to expand your skill set and reach new heights in your career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect with amazing people&lt;/strong&gt;: You will become part of a network of +10,000 Devoteamers spread over 20 countries.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborative Culture&lt;/strong&gt;: Teamwork is at the heart of our organisation. You'll be working side by side with a diverse group of IT experts who share your passion for excellence and will inspire you to think outside the box.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impactful Projects&lt;/strong&gt;: Tackle real-world challenges that matter! From revolutionising business processes to developing innovative solutions, you'll have the chance to make a genuine and positive impact on our clients and the community.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work-Life Balance&lt;/strong&gt;: We believe in a healthy work-life balance, ensuring that you have time to unwind, pursue your hobbies, and spend quality time with loved ones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inspiring and eco-friendly workplace&lt;/strong&gt;: We just moved to an amazing new building. We believe an inspiring workspace fuels creativity and fosters a positive work culture, allowing our employees to reach their full potential. The Wings building is also designed with eco-friendly features and energy-efficient systems. By reducing our ecological footprint, we are contributing to a greener future and aligning our business practices with our environmental values. The building is also very easily accessible by public transportation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive package&lt;/strong&gt;: We offer a competitive salary package with additional benefits like a company car, smartphone, medical insurance, pension plan, net allowance, laptop, meal vouchers, etc. We review our salary grid twice a year to ensure we are in line with the market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Devoteam, we combine strong values – respect, frankness, ambition, entrepreneurship &amp;amp; collaboration - with a fun environment that empowers you to innovate and succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan 3 , 1831 Machelen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 201-500&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10402"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="Security"/>
    <category term="M365"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10055</id>
    <title>Cloud Solution Architect (Sopra Steria)</title>
    <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.373256+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Sopra Steria&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Frédéric La Roche, Recruiter – Sopra Steria Benelux SA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Brussels and Flanders (Culliganlaan 3, 1831 Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 20/11/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sky’s the limit with cloud computing, so you’ll need to use skills of virtualization, containerization, and orchestration using tools like Kubernetes and Docker to design, deploy, and manage cloud-based solutions. We pride ourselves on our secure, compliant, efficient and well-optimized cloud solutions. You’ll feel at home working with cloud-native development, serverless architectures, and DevOps practices. To take cloud adoption to its fullest extent, you’ll use your analytical and governance skills, problem-solving abilities, and cross-functional team collaboration to drive innovation and efficiency in cloud environments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pave the way for cloud adoption and digital transformation with Microsoft Azure’s suite of virtual machines, storage solutions, networking, and databases. Problem-solving, collaboration with cross-functional teams and designing scalable solutions are going to be your key skills. You’ll also familiarize yourself with monitoring tools, and cost management to deliver the continuous integration and delivery, as well as implementing security best practices, quality and compliance that Sopra Steria is known for.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our Architects have the vision and leadership skills to make daring IT decisions that can make digital transformation a reality. Your ability to collaborate across teams and departments and your flexibility to adopt new technologies will help you enhance system performance, scalability, and security. Fulfil your vision at Sopra Steria, and align it with our business development goals. As a Sopra Steria Architect, you’ll have successful projects in your portfolio that can demonstrate your excellent problem solving skills and commitment to continuous learning.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re seeking passionate colleagues who are eager to push the boundaries in digital transformation and technology consulting. At Sopra Steria, you’ll have the opportunity to grow your skills in a constructive, collaborative team environment, working on impactful projects that drive change for our clients. If you thrive on challenge and meet (most of) the qualifications below, we look forward to your application!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll have knowledge and experience of the following:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s or Master’s&amp;nbsp; degree in computer science or a relevant equivalent&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Designing, implementing and supporting cloud projects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Brown- and greenfield approaches&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Azure cloud technologies&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Analysis of complex problems and tackling them with a commercial mindset&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Digital innovation and transformation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Business mindset and creating new opportunity&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;(Pre)Sales&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fluent in English and Dutch/French&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we can offer you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a member of one of Europe’s largest digital solutions providers, you’ll benefit from extensive career development opportunities, both local and international. At the Sopra Steria Academy, you’ll be part of a dynamic network of 56,000 professionals at all stages of their careers. With a wide array of offices to explore, you can find your ideal location and take the next step in your career.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ll become a part of a major Tech player in Europe recognized for its consulting, digital services, and software development. On top of that, you’ll join the Business Line DPS (Digital Platform Services) and join the team of infrastructure and architecture experts: hybrid systems engineers, network and security engineers, Linux consultants, cloud native engineers and cloud solution architects.&lt;br&gt;Our teams help our clients with data center management and data center setup and maintenance. We offer on-premise and cloud solutions, both public and private. This is because we believe in a solution that fits our customers' unique context and business strategy. Often that is a healthy combination of cloud and on-premise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our employees are known for making bold choices and delivering results. Work among high-level professionals at the forefront of corporate software solutions and innovation at Europe’s Leading Digital Service Provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We offer a generous employee benefits package that includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A variety of perks, such as mobility options (including a company car), insurance coverage, meal vouchers, eco-cheques, and more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continuous learning opportunities through the Sopra Steria Academy to support your career development.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to connect with fellow Sopra Steria colleagues at various team events.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;People are the cornerstone of our success. That’s why we aspire to be bolder together. Our goal is to build high-functioning teams and healthy team environments that inspire and help each other to deliver excellence for each of our customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excited about this job opportunity? Ready to shape the world with us? Great! We are looking forward to your application!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to know what happens next?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recruitment process typically begins with the first step, where the recruiter screens candidates based on their qualifications and fit for the role. This is followed by the second step, where candidates undergo more in-depth evaluations, including technical assessments and an interview with the capacity manager to assess both technical skills and team compatibility. The third step involves the company reviewing feedback and aligning on a potential offer. Finally, in the final step, the candidate receives a formal job offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;______&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sopra Steria is an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will be considered for employment without regard to age, ancestry, nationality, color, family or medical leave, gender identity or expression, genetic information, immigration status, marital status, medical condition, national origin, physical or mental disability, political affiliation, protected veteran or military status, race, ethnicity, religion, gender (including pregnancy), sexual orientation or any other characteristic protected by applicable local laws, regulations and ordinances. We foster a work environment that is inclusive and respectful of all differences.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 53&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 501-1000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10055"/>
    <category term="Cloud"/>
    <category term="DevOps"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10004</id>
    <title>Cloud System Engineer (Sopra Steria)</title>
    <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.373145+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Sopra Steria&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Frédéric La Roche, Recruiter – Sopra Steria Benelux SA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Brussels and Flanders (Culliganlaan 3, 1831 Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 16/12/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sky’s the limit with cloud computing, so you’ll need to use skills of virtualization, containerization, and orchestration using tools like Kubernetes and Docker to design, deploy, and manage cloud-based solutions. We pride ourselves on our secure, compliant, efficient and well-optimized cloud solutions. You’ll feel at home working with cloud-native development, serverless architectures, and DevOps practices. To take cloud adoption to its fullest extent, you’ll use your analytical and governance skills, problem-solving abilities, and cross-functional team collaboration to drive innovation and efficiency in cloud environments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Keeping our systems running smoothly and optimally will be your ultimate goal as our (Cloud) System Engineer. Your days will consist of automating and maintaining our systems as well as developing scripts that optimize our infrastructure and align cloud systems to always serve our business goals. You’ll use your expertise in cloud platforms (Azure &amp;amp; AWS), automation frameworks, containerization, virtualization, networking, and security practices to drive digital transformation. Our goal is to build reliable and cost-efficient systems. As a (Cloud) System Engineer, you’ll make it happen by designing, implementing, and supporting scalable cloud environments, streamlining deployment processes and reducing manual interventions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re seeking passionate colleagues who are eager to push the boundaries in digital transformation and technology consulting. At Sopra Steria, you’ll have the opportunity to grow your skills in a constructive, collaborative team environment, working on impactful projects that drive change for our clients. If you thrive on challenge and meet (most of) the qualifications below, we look forward to your application!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You’ll have knowledge and experience of the following:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bachelor’s&amp;nbsp;or Master’s degree in computer science or a relevant equivalent&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;5 years of experience in infrastructure projects&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Eperience with cloud services such as Microsoft Azure, AzureAD, EMS, Office365, AWS etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Broad knowledge of networking, system and information architectures, storage concepts, virtualization, containers, automation, Microsoft Azure, Office 365, security and management&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Scripting and automation: Powershell, VBSript, Bash, Ansible etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with methodologies such as project management, ITIL, etc. or are willing to get certified&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fluent in English and Dutch/French&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What we can offer you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a member of one of Europe’s largest digital solutions providers, you’ll benefit from extensive career development opportunities, both local and international. At the Sopra Steria Academy, you’ll be part of a dynamic network of 56,000 professionals at all stages of their careers. With a wide array of offices to explore, you can find your ideal location and take the next step in your career.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You’ll become a part of a major Tech player in Europe recognized for its consulting, digital services, and software development. On top of that, you’ll join the Business Line DPS (Digital Platform Services) and join the team of infrastructure and architecture experts: hybrid systems engineers, network and security engineers, Linux consultants, cloud native engineers and cloud solution architects.&lt;br&gt;Our teams help our clients with data center management and data center setup and maintenance. We offer on-premise and cloud solutions, both public and private. This is because we believe in a solution that fits our customers' unique context and business strategy. Often that is a healthy combination of cloud and on-premise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our employees are known for making bold choices and delivering results. Work among high-level professionals at the forefront of corporate software solutions and innovation at Europe’s Leading Digital Service Provider.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We offer a generous employee benefits package that includes:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A variety of perks, such as mobility options (including a company car), insurance coverage, meal vouchers, eco-cheques, and more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continuous learning opportunities through the Sopra Steria Academy to support your career development.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to connect with fellow Sopra Steria colleagues at various team events.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;People are the cornerstone of our success. That’s why we aspire to be bolder together. Our goal is to build high-functioning teams and healthy team environments that inspire and help each other to deliver excellence for each of our customers.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excited about this job opportunity? Ready to shape the world with us? Great! We are looking forward to your application!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Want to know what happens next?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The recruitment process typically begins with the first step, where the recruiter screens candidates based on their qualifications and fit for the role. This is followed by the second step, where candidates undergo more in-depth evaluations, including technical assessments and an interview with the capacity manager to assess both technical skills and team compatibility. The third step involves the company reviewing feedback and aligning on a potential offer. Finally, in the final step, the candidate receives a formal job offer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;______&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sopra Steria is an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will be considered for employment without regard to age, ancestry, nationality, color, family or medical leave, gender identity or expression, genetic information, immigration status, marital status, medical condition, national origin, physical or mental disability, political affiliation, protected veteran or military status, race, ethnicity, religion, gender (including pregnancy), sexual orientation or any other characteristic protected by applicable local laws, regulations and ordinances. We foster a work environment that is inclusive and respectful of all differences.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 53&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 501-1000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10004"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="Amazon Web Services (AWS)"/>
    <category term="Microsoft 365 / Office 365"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/12386</id>
    <title>M365 Solution &amp; Change Analyst/Architect (Devoteam)</title>
    <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.373035+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Bob Cobben, Senior Talent Acquisition Specialist – Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Machelen (Culliganlaan 3, 1831 Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 04/08/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like these keywords, you’ll love this role:&lt;br&gt;#M365 #SharePoint #Teams #Yammer #PowerPlatform #Adoption #Change&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s more fundamental in IT than a Digital Workplace that is fully adopted by end users?&lt;br&gt;Develop, design, and build the future with us as a Microsoft 365 Workplace Solution Architect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You will be part of the “Data Integrated Digital Workplace” practice with an in-depth expertise combination on Microsoft’s Modern Workplace (SharePoint and MS 365), Data Business Intelligence (SQL &amp;amp; Azure Data Warehousing and Power BI),and low-code development frameworks on Azure.&lt;br&gt;You and the team share the vision and passion “to create &amp;amp; develop Digital Workplaces with true Business value &amp;amp; adoption” by offering end-users integrated platforms where they find, get pushed and can act upon all the right information, data and documents, at the right time and in the right business context.&lt;br&gt;You will work with Client’s Business &amp;amp; Technical employees to capture, discuss, create, build, deliver &amp;amp; verify solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Profile&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have a broad view on the entire Microsoft 365 “Modern Workplace” portfolio including Teams &amp;amp; SharePoint&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have experience and/or a talent to deliver results-driven workshops with the customer to capture requirements, explain the new way of working that can be realized with out-of-the-box M365, and the benefits that can be realized.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have experience and/or a talent to work with in-depth technical experts to get the defined solutions created.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have experience and/or a talent to guide customers in adopting the solutions on your own or with specialized adoption and change managers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise or affinity with the Microsoft Security, Compliance &amp;amp; Identity solutions to secure customers’ Modern Workplace&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise or affinity with Microsoft Defender and Intune to secure customers’ Endpoints of their Modern Workplace&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise or affinity with the Microsoft Power low-code Platform to further automate and increase productivity in customers’ Modern Workplace&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise or affinity with Front-end and/or Back-end(.NET) development of solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You’re ready to drive change and bring creative tech ideas to life.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You’re either proficient in Dutch or French (or you want to learn) and fluent in English.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Bonus-points] MS 365 certified (or willing to obtain). Certifications in scope: MS-900, MS-600, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Bonus-points] MS Power Platform certified (or willing to obtain). Certifications in scope: PL-900, PL-200, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Bonus-points] MS Security, Compliance &amp;amp; Identity certified (or willing to obtain). Certifications in scope: SC-900, SC-300, etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If you do not feel fully confident that you meet the requirements above, please don’t worry. Just apply. Together we’ll discover what you can bring to the table, in which role you would fit best and how you could potentially grow at Devoteam.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our promises to you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;As a digital native you will have a positive impact at top organizations in Belgium.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Direct access to the Microsoft organization and programs thanks to our global partnership.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prepare to inspire and be inspired by other Devoteamers in tech communities.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We enable local and international collaboration and exchange with other tech leaders and specialists, knowledge sharing, peer-to-peer coaching.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A personalized career plan with training offers in soft- &amp;amp; hard skills and certifications aligned to your needs &amp;amp; expertise.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Our servant leadership supports opportunities to grow your personal brand through blogs, keynote sessions, and more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;#techies in our minds, #creatives in our hearts, #change in our DNA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why choose us?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cutting-edge Technology&lt;/strong&gt;: Embrace the latest advancements in IT and digital technologies as we constantly innovate to stay ahead of the competition. Our commitment to adopting state-of-the-art tools and methodologies ensures that you'll work on projects at the forefront of the industry.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Entrepreneur mindset&lt;/strong&gt;: We value our people over processes. You will develop and grow in an agile and ambitious company where it’s okay to take risks, make mistakes and change plans to find transformative solutions. At the same time, you will learn from the best, building relationships and skills that will last your entire career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Endless Learning Opportunities&lt;/strong&gt;: We value personal and professional growth. Through workshops, conferences, and certifications, we offer the resources needed to expand your skill set and reach new heights in your career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect with amazing people&lt;/strong&gt;: You will become part of a network of +10,000 Devoteamers spread over 20 countries.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborative Culture&lt;/strong&gt;: Teamwork is at the heart of our organisation. You'll be working side by side with a diverse group of IT experts who share your passion for excellence and will inspire you to think outside the box.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impactful Projects&lt;/strong&gt;: Tackle real-world challenges that matter! From revolutionising business processes to developing innovative solutions, you'll have the chance to make a genuine and positive impact on our clients and the community.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work-Life Balance&lt;/strong&gt;: We believe in a healthy work-life balance, ensuring that you have time to unwind, pursue your hobbies, and spend quality time with loved ones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inspiring and eco-friendly workplace&lt;/strong&gt;: We just moved to an amazing new building. We believe an inspiring workspace fuels creativity and fosters a positive work culture, allowing our employees to reach their full potential. The Wings building is also designed with eco-friendly features and energy-efficient systems. By reducing our ecological footprint, we are contributing to a greener future and aligning our business practices with our environmental values. The building is also very easily accessible by public transportation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive package&lt;/strong&gt;: We offer a competitive salary package with additional benefits like a company car, smartphone, medical insurance, pension plan, net allowance, laptop, meal vouchers, etc. We review our salary grid twice a year to ensure we are in line with the market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Devoteam, we combine strong values – respect, frankness, ambition, entrepreneurship &amp;amp; collaboration - with a fun environment that empowers you to innovate and succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan 3 , 1831 Machelen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 201-500&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/12386"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="Security"/>
    <category term="Pre-Sales Consulting"/>
    <category term="M365"/>
    <category term="Power Platform"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/14439</id>
    <title>Functioneel analist (KBC Bank &amp; Verzekering)</title>
    <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.372914+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: KBC Bank &amp;amp; Verzekering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Isabelle De Meyst, Expert employer branding – KBC Bank &amp;amp; Verzekering&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Leuven (Leuven)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on 12/01/2026, last change 12/01/2026&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wat houdt deze vacature in?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;p&gt;Regelgevende rapportering is een boeiend domein dat voortdurend in beweging is. Als ervaren professional binnen regulatory reporting weet je dat wellicht al. Het team dat jij versterkt, ontwikkelt datastromen, corrigeert gegevens en garandeert de nauwkeurigheid van data in overeenstemming met de regelgeving. Samen met je collega’s, werk je onder meer aan deze regelgevende rapportering: FinRep, CoRep, SHS, SRB, ALM, Basel IV, Solvency II, Credit Risk,.....&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Versterk jij ons binnenkort als functioneel analist? Je kan rekenen op fijne collega’s, uitdaging en een interessante, internationale werkcontext.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wat verwachten we van jou?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je verzamelt en documenteert de functionele requirements van stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Met behulp van SQL voer je een analyse en een kritische data mapping uit.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je draagt bij tot de kwaliteitscontrole van de data en lost bugs op.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je vertaalt de functionele vereisten naar het datamodel voor correcte rapportage.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Tijdens de ontwikkelings- en testfase volg je mee op, analyseer je bugs en waak je erover dat het opgeleverde resultaat in overeenstemming is met de functionele vereisten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jouw troeven?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je hebt een bachelor- of masterdiploma en minstens 2 tot 4 jaar ervaring als functioneel analist.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je werkte reeds in een agile- / scrum-werkomgeving, waarbij je betrokken was bij regulatoire rapportering zoals FinRep, CoRep, ALM, Credit Risk, Basel IV...&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Net zoals je collega’s hou je ervan om samen met anderen tot nauwkeurige resultaten en elegante oplossingen te komen. Jouw aanpak? Proactief, kritisch en wendbaar.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je communiceert doeltreffend in het Nederlands en Engels, zowel mondeling als schriftelijk.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je werkt vlot met SQL.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Het is een meerwaarde als je al vertrouwd bent met ETL, datawarehousing, datamodellering en testen, maar dat is geen must.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Deze handige tools ken je, of wil je leren kennen: GitHub - Jenkins - ServiceNow - Job Scheduling Tools - Jira&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h4&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wat hebben we je te bieden?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bij ons ben je zeker van een &lt;strong&gt;uitstekende onboarding, collegialiteit en een aangename werksfeer&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Doorheen je hele loopbaan bij KBC moedigen we je aan om verder te groeien als persoon en als professional. Je kan &lt;strong&gt;opleidingen volgen&lt;/strong&gt; waarin je je hard en soft skills verder aanscherpt.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je werkplek is vlot bereikbaar met het openbaar vervoer. Je kan ook deels vanuit een ander hoofdkantoor werken of van thuis uit.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Flexibele werkuren&lt;/strong&gt; helpen je om je werk en je privéleven op elkaar af te stemmen.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We bieden jou een contract van onbepaalde duur en een competitief loon aangevuld met extralegale voordelen. Sounds familiar? Tuurlijk, dit lees je in elke vacature. KBC maakt het verschil met een &lt;strong&gt;uitgebreid flexpakket&lt;/strong&gt;. Te uitgebreid om hier uit de doeken te doen. De verschillende voordelen - groot en klein - bespreken we graag met jou tijdens je sollicitatiegesprek.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Havenlaan 2&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 11&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 10000+&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Financial services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/14439"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term="ETL / Datawarehouse"/>
    <category term="Jenkins"/>
    <category term="ServiceNow"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10403</id>
    <title>Azure Data Engineer (Devoteam)</title>
    <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.372780+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Laurent  Huygens, Talent Acquisition Manager – Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Machelen (3 Cullinganlaan 1831 Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 22/12/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you like these keywords, you’ll love this role:&lt;br&gt;#M365 #Entra #Defender #Purview #Intune&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;What’s more fundamental in IT these days than a Digital Workplace that is fully secured and compliant by end users?&lt;br&gt;Develop, design, and build the future with us as a Microsoft 365 Workplace Security Architect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a Workplace Security Architect, you know the solutions that can help in increasing the workplace security maturity. You know what Zero-trust is and how you can use Microsoft technology to protect customers against cyberthreats. You will work with Client’s Business &amp;amp; Technical employees to capture, discuss, create, build, deliver &amp;amp; verify solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For this position, we’re looking for &lt;strong&gt;all seniority levels&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have a broad view of the Modern Workplace building blocks, from classic solutions to Microsoft 365.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have a broad view of all the Microsoft 365 Defender Solutions&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You have expertise on how to secure Endpoints, Identities, Apps and Data with Microsoft 365 Defender, Intune, Entra and Purview.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You can design an entire architecture that protects the corporate data and prevent data loss.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Must-have] You are an expert in one or more Microsoft (365) solutions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise with Defender for Cloud and/or Microsoft Sentinel.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have experience and/or a talent to deliver results-driven workshops with the customer to capture requirements, explain the new way of working that can be realized with out-of-the-box M365, and the benefits that can be realized.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You have expertise or affinity with the Microsoft Power low-code Platform or Ometa to further automate and increase productivity in&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You’re ready to drive change and bring creative tech ideas to life.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Nice-to-have] You’re either proficient in Dutch or French (or you want to learn) and fluent in English.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;[Bonus-points] MS certified (or willing to obtain). Certifications in scope: SC-100, SC-300, SC-400, MS-102, MS-203 etc.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you do not feel fully confident that you meet the requirements above, please don’t worry. Just apply. Together we’ll discover what you can bring to the table, in which role you would fit best and how you could potentially grow at Devoteam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our promises to you&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;As a digital native you will have a positive impact at top organizations in Belgium.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Direct access to the Microsoft organization and programs thanks to our global partnership.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Prepare to inspire and be inspired by other Devoteamers in tech communities.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;We enable local and international collaboration and exchange with other tech leaders and specialists, knowledge sharing, peer-to-peer coaching.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A personalized career plan with training offers in soft- &amp;amp; hard skills and certifications aligned to your needs &amp;amp; expertise.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Our servant leadership supports opportunities to grow your personal brand through blogs, keynote sessions, and more.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;#techies in our minds, #creatives in our hearts, #change in our DNA.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why choose us?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cutting-edge Technology&lt;/strong&gt;: Embrace the latest advancements in IT and digital technologies as we constantly innovate to stay ahead of the competition. Our commitment to adopting state-of-the-art tools and methodologies ensures that you'll work on projects at the forefront of the industry.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Entrepreneur mindset&lt;/strong&gt;: We value our people over processes. You will develop and grow in an agile and ambitious company where it’s okay to take risks, make mistakes and change plans to find transformative solutions. At the same time, you will learn from the best, building relationships and skills that will last your entire career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Endless Learning Opportunities&lt;/strong&gt;: We value personal and professional growth. Through workshops, conferences, and certifications, we offer the resources needed to expand your skill set and reach new heights in your career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect with amazing people&lt;/strong&gt;: You will become part of a network of +10,000 Devoteamers spread over 20 countries.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborative Culture&lt;/strong&gt;: Teamwork is at the heart of our organisation. You'll be working side by side with a diverse group of IT experts who share your passion for excellence and will inspire you to think outside the box.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impactful Projects&lt;/strong&gt;: Tackle real-world challenges that matter! From revolutionising business processes to developing innovative solutions, you'll have the chance to make a genuine and positive impact on our clients and the community.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work-Life Balance&lt;/strong&gt;: We believe in a healthy work-life balance, ensuring that you have time to unwind, pursue your hobbies, and spend quality time with loved ones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inspiring and eco-friendly workplace&lt;/strong&gt;: We just moved to an amazing new building. We believe an inspiring workspace fuels creativity and fosters a positive work culture, allowing our employees to reach their full potential. The Wings building is also designed with eco-friendly features and energy-efficient systems. By reducing our ecological footprint, we are contributing to a greener future and aligning our business practices with our environmental values. The building is also very easily accessible by public transportation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive package&lt;/strong&gt;: We offer a competitive salary package with additional benefits like a company car, smartphone, medical insurance, pension plan, net allowance, laptop, meal vouchers, etc. We review our salary grid twice a year to ensure we are in line with the market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Devoteam, we combine strong values – respect, frankness, ambition, entrepreneurship &amp;amp; collaboration - with a fun environment that empowers you to innovate and succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan 3 , 1831 Machelen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 201-500&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10403"/>
    <category term="Cloud"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="Business Intelligence"/>
    <category term="SSIS"/>
    <category term="Microsoft SQL Server"/>
    <category term="Power BI"/>
    <category term="SSAS / SSRS"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10485</id>
    <title>Analytics Engineer (Datashift)</title>
    <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.372674+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Datashift&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Fred Thiebaut, Recruiter – Datashift&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Mechelen (Oude Brusselsestraat 14, 2800 Mechelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 11/12/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Datashift, a rapidly expanding team dedicated to providing data-driven solutions for business challenges, is seeking a talented &lt;strong&gt;Analytics Engineer&lt;/strong&gt; to join us.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this role, you will play a crucial part in translating client needs into sustainable data solutions, encompassing ETL processes, Infrastructure as Code, interfaces, and pipelines.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Designing data solutions, balancing cost and maintainability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborating with Data Scientists, BI specialists, and Business Consultants to deliver value.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Staying abreast of the latest developments in data technology and actively sharing knowledge with colleagues.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Monitoring the quality and stability of data solutions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Mentoring and coaching other Analyticals Engineer.&lt;br&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do you have &lt;strong&gt;4 to 6 years&lt;/strong&gt; of experience, including at least &lt;strong&gt;2 years&lt;/strong&gt; in a cloud environment? Do you possess a passion for approaching projects from an end-to-end data perspective? We are delighted to receive your personal application and we’ll contact you for an interview and a (virtual) cup of coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You can adeptly apply diverse data modeling styles and collaborate with our customers to develop the optimal data model for their needs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You grasp data structures &amp;amp; formats and are familiar with popular (cloud) data warehouses.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You navigate DBT with expertise, effortlessly crafting a new project, playing with all the DBT-blocks to build a castle from the ground up.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deep knowledge of SQL;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have a proven track record of effortlessly incorporating DevOps best practices such as CI/CD, IaC, and unit testing. CI/CD, which may sound like a secret code, is a realm you navigate with ease. You not only grasp its steps but can also articulate why it's indispensable for any data project. Moreover, you possess the skills to autonomously set it up.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You approach challenges with an analytical and solution-oriented mindset, and you're well-acquainted with agile methodologies and collaborative teamwork.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with Docker and PySpark is a plus;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience with dataframe API’s in Python (Panda’s, Polars, ...);&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fluent in Dutch and/or French and English.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your growth path&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Datashift is a firm believer in growing through its people. We will guide and support you providing many opportunities to develop and grow in the direction you want. However, we equally believe that it is you who takes ownership of your growth. That is why we give you the tools and the driving seat, it's up to you to do seize the opportunity.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One thing is for sure, surrounded by an entrepreneurial team, many opportunities will present themselves to deepen your expertise knowledge or broaden your Horizon in Data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this role, you are on the track to become a master in leading Data Engineering solutions for our clients. Whilst collaborating within Datashift on existing competence centers or helping to establish new practices. Making sure you and we keep up with the advancements in Data engineering.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A highly entrepreneurial team;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A no-nonsense working environment with a focus on high quality;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent terms of employment (including company car, fuel card, meal vouchers &amp;amp; bonus);&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fringe benefits including continuous training that builds and extends professional, technical and management skills in all areas;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to grow together with Datashift in terms of capabilities as well as financial benefits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Oude Brusselsestraat 14, 2800 Mechelen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 9&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 51-200&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10485"/>
    <category term="Cloud"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term="Python"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/15528</id>
    <title>Senior Data Analyst - Power Platforms (Pauwels Consulting)</title>
    <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.372562+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Pauwels Consulting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Jan Vanden Boer, Digital Service Lead – Pauwels Consulting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Gent (Gent)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on 26/01/2026, last change 26/01/2026&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;This role sits at the core of a large-scale logistics and distribution center that ensures the continuous availability of spare parts for mission-critical operations across Europe. You will work in a highly operational, shop-floor-driven environment where data solutions are built directly from real production needs. The position combines hands-on analytics with team-level responsibility, acting as a technical anchor and backup for the team lead.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Translate operational and production input into concrete data solutions, dashboards, and tools&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design, build, and maintain analytics solutions using Power Platform and modern data tooling&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Act as a technical reference within the analytics team, supporting planning and Scrum coordination&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate closely with shop-floor stakeholders to turn real-world needs into data-driven improvements&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Ensure data availability, reliability, and usability for logistics and distribution operations&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Contribute to the continuous improvement of data maturity across the distribution center&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What are we looking for?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have at least 3+ years of hands-on experience with &lt;strong&gt;Power Platform&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;SQL&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;Python&lt;/strong&gt; (in that order of importance)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have proven experience as a &lt;strong&gt;Data Analyst in an operational or logistics-driven environment&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are fluent in &lt;strong&gt;Dutch&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;English&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are available to work &lt;strong&gt;full-time onsite in Ghent&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have experience working in an Agile or Scrum-based team setup&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You bring sufficient technical depth to support and back up a team lead role&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Nice to Haves&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Knowledge of &lt;strong&gt;VBA&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience acting as Scrum Master or coordinating sprint planning&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Exposure to large-scale warehouse, supply chain, or distribution center environments&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do we offer?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Location: &lt;strong&gt;Ghent&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Working model: &lt;strong&gt;Fully onsite (no remote work)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Contract type: Open to both permanent employees and freelancers&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Start date: ASAP, Long-term engagement&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Lambroekstraat&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 37&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 501-1000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Staffing &amp;amp; Recruiting&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/15528"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term="Python"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10115</id>
    <title>Data Scientist Engineer  (Devoteam)</title>
    <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.372450+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Laurent  Huygens, Talent Acquisition Manager – Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Machelen (3 Culliganlaan 1831 Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 15/12/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you passionate about data-driven platforms, machine learning models, and innovative applications? As a Data Scientist/Engineer at Devoteam, you'll play a hands-on role in delivering impactful solutions across various clients and industries. Each mission we undertake has clear deliverables and deadlines, ensuring you gain diverse experience. For example, one month you might develop a predictive maintenance model, and the next, a customer segmentation model for a retail client.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Key Responsibilities:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Platform Setup:&lt;/strong&gt; Design and implement robust data platforms using Azure, AWS or Google Cloud and Databricks.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Data Management:&lt;/strong&gt; Gather, prepare, and manage data for analysis.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Model Research:&lt;/strong&gt; Investigate and select appropriate machine learning models.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ML Modeling:&lt;/strong&gt; Develop and refine machine learning models.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Client Collaboration:&lt;/strong&gt; Spend approximately 50% of your time working directly with clients, either independently or as part of a team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your Role:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Build and maintain data platforms and pipelines using Azure, AWS or Google Cloud, Databricks, and Python.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Develop predictive and machine learning models tailored to client needs.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Advise clients on translating their business requirements into technical solutions using machine learning techniques.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Stay updated on the latest trends in machine learning and AI, sharing insights with clients.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Act as a strategic partner to client Data Science teams, helping them navigate their challenges and aspirations.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Inspire clients with new data-driven opportunities.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bring best practices in Git, DevOps, and CICD to enhance client data platforms.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Collaborate with Data Scientists, Data Engineers, and Business Stakeholders.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Represent Devoteam both online and offline, showcasing our expertise.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional Information:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why choose us?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cutting-edge Technology&lt;/strong&gt;: Embrace the latest advancements in IT and digital technologies as we constantly innovate to stay ahead of the competition. Our commitment to adopting state-of-the-art tools and methodologies ensures that you'll work on projects at the forefront of the industry.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Entrepreneur mindset&lt;/strong&gt;: We value our people over processes. You will develop and grow in an agile and ambitious company where it’s okay to take risks, make mistakes and change plans to find transformative solutions. At the same time, you will learn from the best, building relationships and skills that will last your entire career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Endless Learning Opportunities&lt;/strong&gt;: We value personal and professional growth. Through workshops, conferences, and certifications, we offer the resources needed to expand your skill set and reach new heights in your career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect with amazing people&lt;/strong&gt;: You will become part of a network of +10,000 Devoteamers spread over 20 countries.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborative Culture&lt;/strong&gt;: Teamwork is at the heart of our organisation. You'll be working side by side with a diverse group of IT experts who share your passion for excellence and will inspire you to think outside the box.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impactful Projects&lt;/strong&gt;: Tackle real-world challenges that matter! From revolutionising business processes to developing innovative solutions, you'll have the chance to make a genuine and positive impact on our clients and the community.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work-Life Balance&lt;/strong&gt;: We believe in a healthy work-life balance, ensuring that you have time to unwind, pursue your hobbies, and spend quality time with loved ones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inspiring and eco-friendly workplace&lt;/strong&gt;: We just moved to an amazing new building. We believe an inspiring workspace fuels creativity and fosters a positive work culture, allowing our employees to reach their full potential. The Wings building is also designed with eco-friendly features and energy-efficient systems. By reducing our ecological footprint, we are contributing to a greener future and aligning our business practices with our environmental values. The building is also very easily accessible by public transportation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive package&lt;/strong&gt;: We offer a competitive salary package with additional benefits like a company car, smartphone, medical insurance, pension plan, net allowance, laptop, meal vouchers, etc. We review our salary grid twice a year to ensure we are in line with the market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Devoteam, we combine strong values – respect, frankness, ambition, entrepreneurship &amp;amp; collaboration - with a fun environment that empowers you to innovate and succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan 3 , 1831 Machelen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 201-500&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10115"/>
    <category term="Artificial intelligence"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="Machine Learning"/>
    <category term="Python"/>
    <category term="Amazon Web Services (AWS)"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/12710</id>
    <title>Data Science and AI expert (Sopra Steria)</title>
    <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.372342+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Sopra Steria&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Frédéric La Roche, Recruiter – Sopra Steria Benelux SA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Brussels &amp;amp; Flanders (Culliganlaan 3b 1831 Machelen Belgium )&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 13/11/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Are you passionate about using data science and AI to real-world problems? At Sopra Steria, we’re looking for an experienced and versatile professional to help lead the design and delivery of advanced analytics and AI solutions across a wide range of domainssuch as public services, utilities, healthcare, mobility, and beyond.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this role, you will work on impactful projects from ideation to delivery. You’ll collaborate closely with both technical and business stakeholders transforming challenges into actionable insights and production-ready solutions. Whether it’s designing an optimization algorithm, building an LLM-based assistant, or delivering a forecasting pipeline, you’ll help clients unlock value from data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re looking for someone who combines deep technical expertise with the maturity to take ownership, work autonomously, and guide teams and clients through the ever-evolving AI landscape.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;We’re seeking passionate colleagues who are eager to push the boundaries of digital transformation with AI. If you recognize yourself in most of the following, we’d love to talk:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have &lt;strong&gt;at least 5 years of experienc&lt;/strong&gt;e in delivering real-world AI and data science solutions in production environments.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You are proficient in &lt;strong&gt;Python &lt;/strong&gt;and comfortable with frameworks like scikit-learn, TensorFlow, PyTorch, or similar.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have practical experience with &lt;strong&gt;machine learning, and ideally exposure to domains like natural language processing, computer vision, predictive analytics, LLM’s &lt;/strong&gt;or&lt;strong&gt; optimization.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You’ve worked with &lt;strong&gt;at least one major cloud provider &lt;/strong&gt;(Azure, AWS, or GCP), and understand how to bring models into production securely and efficiently.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You understand how to balance model performance with business relevance, and how to translate analytical outcomes into &lt;strong&gt;actionable results&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You enjoy working in a team, guiding junior colleagues, and &lt;strong&gt;collaborating with clients&lt;/strong&gt; to define solution architectures and technical roadmaps.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You’re comfortable interacting with stakeholders and can &lt;strong&gt;communicate complex concepts &lt;/strong&gt;clearly and persuasively.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience in &lt;strong&gt;project ownership&lt;/strong&gt;, technical leadership, or contributing to AI strategies.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;You are fluent in &lt;strong&gt;English&lt;/strong&gt;, and speak either &lt;strong&gt;Dutch or French&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What We Can Offer You&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A key role in one of Europe’s leading digital transformation companies, where innovation meets real-world impact.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to work on high-impact projects in AI and advanced analytics across industries and public institutions.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A culture of collaboration and continuous learning, supported by an expert network of consultants, architects, and engineers.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Access to our Sopra Steria Academy, with a wide range of training opportunities and certifications.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A hybrid and flexible working model, with access to offices across Belgium.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Career development opportunities both locally and internationally, within a growing Data &amp;amp; AI practice.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;Our employees are known for making bold choices and delivering results. Work among high-level professionals at the forefront of corporate software solutions and innovation at Europe’s Leading Digital Service Provider.  &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We offer a generous employee benefits package that includes:&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A variety of perks, such as mobility options (including a company car), insurance coverage, meal vouchers, eco-cheques, and more.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continuous learning opportunities through the Sopra Steria Academy to support your career development.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to connect with fellow Sopra Steria colleagues at various team events. &amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;People are the cornerstone of our success. That’s why we aspire to be bolder together. Our goal is to build high-functioning teams and healthy team environments that inspire and help each other to deliver excellence for each of our customers.  &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Excited about this job opportunity? Ready to shape the world with us? Great! We are looking forward to your application! &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At&amp;nbsp;OptimAI, we combine the best of both worlds:&amp;nbsp;data science&amp;nbsp;and&amp;nbsp;supply chain optimization. You will be part of a forward-thinking team where you can shape the future of data science and supply chain management. This is an excellent opportunity to make a real difference and grow your career in a field that is rapidly evolving and in high demand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you thrive on challenge, continuous learning, and want to make an impact in a fast-growing field, apply now to join the&amp;nbsp;OptimAI Team.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;______&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sopra Steria is an equal opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will be considered for employment without regard to age, ancestry, nationality, color, family or medical leave, gender identity or expression, genetic information, immigration status, marital status, medical condition, national origin, physical or mental disability, political affiliation, protected veteran or military status, race, ethnicity, religion, gender (including pregnancy), sexual orientation or any other characteristic protected by applicable local laws, regulations and ordinances. We foster a work environment that is inclusive and respectful of all differences.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 53&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 501-1000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/12710"/>
    <category term="Python"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10562</id>
    <title>Senior Azure BI &amp; Data Engineer (Datashift)</title>
    <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.372227+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Datashift&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Fred Thiebaut, Recruiter – Datashift&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Mechelen (Oude Brusselsestraat 14, 2800 Mechelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 12/11/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Datashift is a fast-growing consultancy team with a focus on delivering solutions that answer business questions with data and facts. For one of our fastest growing practices, we are looking for a skilled &lt;strong&gt;Azure BI &amp;amp; Data Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Do you have at least&lt;strong&gt; 4 to 6 years of experience?&lt;/strong&gt; Do you love to work on projects and look at them from an end-to-end data perspective. Then we are delighted to receive your personal application and we’ll contact you for an interview and a (virtual) cup of coffee.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your responsibilities&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Leverage your Azure expertise to credibly translate customer needs into components and best practices within the Azure Data Platform.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Serve as the primary internal and external contact for specialized Azure expertise, with the opportunity to progress toward an Architect role.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Design and build data solutions within the Azure framework, making the trade-off between cost and maintainability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;You thrive on collaborating with colleagues and leverage your expertise to maximize your impact within our organization.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay up to date with technical developments, particularly those related to Azure, and quickly identify new features that can add value to data solutions.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Your qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;You have 4+ years of hands-on experience in the Microsoft BI ecosystem (Azure Data Factory, Azure Synapse Analytics, Databricks, Microsoft Fabric, Analysis Services en SQL Server Integration Services), preferably within an Azure cloud environment.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Demonstrated experience in building and optimizing ETL/ELT data pipelines and integrating data from diverse sources (also api’s).&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Deep understanding of modern data architecture concepts, including Data Warehouses, the Kimball methodology, and Data Lakehouses, with hands-on experience and best practices in these areas.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;SQL is your Swiss army knife for data transformation, and you’re also well-versed in Python to tackle any data challenge that comes your way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Our offer&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A highly entrepreneurial team;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A no-nonsense working environment with a focus on high quality;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Excellent terms of employment (including company car, fuel card, meal vouchers &amp;amp; bonus);&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Fringe benefits including continuous training that builds and extends professional, technical and management skills in all areas;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;The opportunity to grow together with Datashift in terms of capabilities as well as financial benefits.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Oude Brusselsestraat 14, 2800 Mechelen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 9&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 51-200&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10562"/>
    <category term="Cloud"/>
    <category term="SQL"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="ETL / Datawarehouse"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10398</id>
    <title>Data Engineer ( AWS, Azure or GCP) (Devoteam)</title>
    <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.372100+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Laurent  Huygens, Talent Acquisition Manager – Devoteam&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Machelen (3 Cullinganlaan 1831 Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 12/11/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Job Description&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As a &lt;strong&gt;Data Engineer&lt;/strong&gt;, you will build and share knowledge with your colleagues. With initiatives like our knowledge sharing sessions, you have various chances to bond and exchange ideas with colleagues, and keep up to date with the latest developments in the field.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You love working with data and are familiar with multiple data platforms and enjoy developing spark applications. You will work in a multidisciplinary team, including data scientists, data architects, analysts, ...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Qualifications&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you are&amp;nbsp;a &lt;strong&gt;Data Engineer &lt;/strong&gt;and &lt;strong&gt;fascinated by Data &lt;/strong&gt;and can bring :&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Requirements:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;A good knowledge on one or multiple programming languages: Scala, Python...&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;A good knowledge on one or multiple technologies:&amp;nbsp; Spark, Kafka, Nifi...&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Experience working on one or multiple Cloud Data platforms (Databricks, Azure, AWS, Google, Cloudera)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Good communication skills&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;Fluency in Dutch or French (one of these languages is mandatory) and English&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Additional Information&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Why choose us?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cutting-edge Technology&lt;/strong&gt;: Embrace the latest advancements in IT and digital technologies as we constantly innovate to stay ahead of the competition. Our commitment to adopting state-of-the-art tools and methodologies ensures that you'll work on projects at the forefront of the industry.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Entrepreneur mindset&lt;/strong&gt;: We value our people over processes. You will develop and grow in an agile and ambitious company where it’s okay to take risks, make mistakes and change plans to find transformative solutions. At the same time, you will learn from the best, building relationships and skills that will last your entire career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Endless Learning Opportunities&lt;/strong&gt;: We value personal and professional growth. Through workshops, conferences, and certifications, we offer the resources needed to expand your skill set and reach new heights in your career.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Connect with amazing people&lt;/strong&gt;: You will become part of a network of +10,000 Devoteamers spread over 20 countries.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Collaborative Culture&lt;/strong&gt;: Teamwork is at the heart of our organisation. You'll be working side by side with a diverse group of IT experts who share your passion for excellence and will inspire you to think outside the box.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Impactful Projects&lt;/strong&gt;: Tackle real-world challenges that matter! From revolutionising business processes to developing innovative solutions, you'll have the chance to make a genuine and positive impact on our clients and the community.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Work-Life Balance&lt;/strong&gt;: We believe in a healthy work-life balance, ensuring that you have time to unwind, pursue your hobbies, and spend quality time with loved ones.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Inspiring and eco-friendly workplace&lt;/strong&gt;: We just moved to an amazing new building. We believe an inspiring workspace fuels creativity and fosters a positive work culture, allowing our employees to reach their full potential. The Wings building is also designed with eco-friendly features and energy-efficient systems. By reducing our ecological footprint, we are contributing to a greener future and aligning our business practices with our environmental values. The building is also very easily accessible by public transportation.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Competitive package&lt;/strong&gt;: We offer a competitive salary package with additional benefits like a company car, smartphone, medical insurance, pension plan, net allowance, laptop, meal vouchers, etc. We review our salary grid twice a year to ensure we are in line with the market.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;p&gt;At Devoteam, we combine strong values – respect, frankness, ambition, entrepreneurship &amp;amp; collaboration - with a fun environment that empowers you to innovate and succeed.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan 3 , 1831 Machelen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 7&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 201-500&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10398"/>
    <category term="Cloud"/>
    <category term="Azure"/>
    <category term="Big data management"/>
    <category term="ETL / Datawarehouse"/>
    <category term="Machine Learning"/>
    <category term="Amazon Web Services (AWS)"/>
    <category term="Docker"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10061</id>
    <title>Senior Data Scientist (Sopra Steria)</title>
    <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.371950+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Sopra Steria&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Frédéric La Roche, Recruiter – Sopra Steria Benelux SA&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Brussels/Flanders (Culliganlaan 3, 1831 Machelen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 30/10/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;Het Data&amp;amp;Ai team van Sopra Steria is momenteel op zoek naar een &lt;strong&gt;Senior Data Scientist&lt;/strong&gt;. We zoeken een collega met een passie voor &lt;strong&gt;data science&lt;/strong&gt; &amp;amp; &lt;strong&gt;AI&lt;/strong&gt;, die graag werkt aan concrete businessprojecten binnen een brede waaier aan domeinen en toepassingen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In deze rol werk je nauw samen met andere Data &amp;amp; AI collega's van &lt;strong&gt;Sopra Steria&lt;/strong&gt;, maar ook met de interne teams van onze klanten. Je neemt het voortouw en neemt actief deel aan verschillende advanced analytics &amp;amp; AI-projecten, van de ideefase tot de effectieve oplevering. Bij elke stap zorg je voor de kwaliteit van de analytische oplossing én de toepasbaarheid richting de business stakeholders.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Klinkt dit als jouw ideale dagelijkse uitdaging? Wacht dan niet langer.. We leren je graag verder kennen!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Wat kunnen we jou aanbieden?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Je wordt deel van een toonaangevende Tech-speler in Europa, erkend voor consulting, digital services en software development.&lt;br&gt;Je werkt samen met high-level professionals die durven te kiezen voor innovatieve oplossingen en die gaan voor echte resultaten.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daarnaast maak je deel uit van ons Data &amp;amp; AI team, waar we ondernemingen en instellingen helpen om meer data driven te worden.&lt;br&gt;We ondersteunen onze klanten bij het verhogen van hun business efficiency en het creëren van impact met data.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We bieden een volledig portfolio aan Services &amp;amp; Solutions om organisaties te ontzorgen in elke stap van hun transitie:van het definiëren en implementeren van een data strategy en governance, over het opzetten van data platforms,tot het visualiseren van dashboards en het toepassen van de nieuwste data science en artificial intelligence methodologieën.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Klaar voor de volgende stap in je carrière? Dan wijzen we je graag in de juiste richting. Met kantoren in bijna 30 landen die je leiden naar plaatsen waar je nog nooit bent geweest. Wil je liever intern groeien? Ook dat is mogelijk. We dagen je uit om jezelf te blijven uitdagen en zo telkens de beste versie van jezelf te zijn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We zijn op zoek naar collega’s die graag de grenzen verleggen binnen digital transformation en technology consulting.&lt;br&gt;Bij Sopra Steria krijg je de kans om je vaardigheden verder te ontwikkelen in een hechte teamomgeving, waar je meewerkt aan impactvolle projecten die echte verandering brengen voor onze klanten.&lt;br&gt;Als jij houdt van een uitdaging en je herkent jezelf in (het merendeel van) onderstaande punten, dan kijken we uit naar jouw sollicitatie!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Je hebt kennis en ervaring met het volgende:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je hebt meerdere jaren ervaring in het bouwen en opleveren van diverse data science &amp;amp; AI toepassingen/oplossingen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je begrijpt dat organisaties vandaag het maximale uit hun beschikbare informatie moeten halen om deze om te zetten in waarde. Je hebt de nodige vaardigheden verworven via eerdere ervaringen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je bent bedreven in Python (andere programmeertalen zijn een pluspunt)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je hebt gewerkt met minstens één cloud provider&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je wordt gemotiveerd door het behalen van concrete resultaten en deliverables. Je wil een tastbaar verschil maken voor de organisaties waarvoor je werkt, en je apprecieert het als jouw bijdrage wordt erkend&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je kan zelfstandig werken, maar waardeert ook samenwerking. Je bent open-minded en durft je mening op een constructieve manier te delen&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Je hebt een hele goede kennis van het Engels en&amp;nbsp;bent ook vlot in Nederlands of Frans&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Je krijgt een uitgebreid pakket voordelen, waaronder:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Een reeks voordelen, zoals mobiliteitsopties (waaronder een bedrijfswagen), verzekeringsdekking, maaltijdcheques, ecocheques en meer.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Voortdurende leermogelijkheden via de Sopra Steria Academy om je carrièreontwikkeling te ondersteunen.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;De mogelijkheid om in contact te komen met collega's van Sopra Steria tijdens verschillende teamevenementen.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lijkt deze job iets voor jou?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ben je klaar om met ons de wereld vorm te geven? Fantastisch! We kijken nu al uit naar jouw sollicitatie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;______&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sopra Steria is een werkgever die gelijke kansen biedt. Alle gekwalificeerde sollicitanten worden in aanmerking genomen voor een job zonder rekening te houden met leeftijd, afkomst, nationaliteit, huidskleur, verlof voor familie- of medische zorg, geslachtsidentiteit of -uitdrukking, genetische informatie, immigratiestatus, burgerlijke staat, medische toestand, nationale herkomst, fysieke of mentale handicap, politieke voorkeur, beschermde veteranen- of militaire status, ras, etniciteit, religie, geslacht (inclusief zwangerschap), seksuele geaardheid of enig ander kenmerk dat wordt beschermd door toepasselijke lokale wetten, voorschriften en verordeningen. We koesteren een werkomgeving die inclusief is en alle verschillen respecteert.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Culliganlaan &lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 53&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 501-1000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Information Technology &amp;amp; Services&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/10061"/>
    <category term="Artificial intelligence"/>
    <category term="Python"/>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/14750</id>
    <title>cloud data platform architect (Port of Antwerp-Bruges)</title>
    <updated>2026-02-08T08:30:34.350947+00:00</updated>
    <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Bedrijf: Port of Antwerp-Bruges&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Recruiter: Thierry Cobbaut,  Talent &amp;amp; Development expert – Port of Antwerp-Bruges&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Locatie: Antwerpen (Zaha Hadidplein 1. B-2030 Antwerpen)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Published on more than 1 month, last change 27/11/2025&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Rol&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Wil je graag mee het beleid ontwikkelen en implementeren rond onze data fabric?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jouw uitdaging&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Als (Cloud) Data Platform Architect maak je deel uit van het Digital team, waar je een rol speelt in de digitale transformatie van onze organisatie. Je ontwikkelt en implementeert het beleid rond onze data fabric, en organiseert de operationele werking ervan met focus op stabiliteit, schaalbaarheid en ondersteuning van de business noden.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Een greep uit jouw gevarieerde takenpakket:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je definieert samen met collega’s een moderne, flexibele data platformarchitectuur die snel kan inspelen op veranderende businessnoden. Je zorgt ervoor dat de data fabric robuust én toekomstgericht is, en nieuwe technologische evoluties zoals AI, machine learning en automation ten volle kan ondersteunen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je analyseert proactief de noden, wensen en opportuniteiten binnen de organisatie en vertaalt deze naar schaalbare, duurzame oplossingen die breed gedragen worden door de stakeholders.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je fungeert als centraal aanspreekpunt voor de data platformarchitectuur en adviseert stakeholders op een pragmatische en risicobewuste manier, met oog voor effectiviteit, efficiëntie en kostenefficiëntie.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je werkt nauw samen met het data streaming team en data engineers om performante, schaalbare en onderhoudsvriendelijke data pipelines op te zetten. Je werkt ook nauw samen met data governance om datakwaliteit, integriteit en naleving van regelgeving te waarborgen. Daarnaast ondersteun je het data science team door betrouwbare data aan te leveren en geautomatiseerde data pipelines op te zetten voor efficiënte modelontwikkeling en -beheer.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je initieert en leidt verbetertrajecten die ons dataplatform versterken. Je volgt deze initiatieven projectmatig op, van ideevorming tot succesvolle release. Je kan deze initiatieven ook zelf implementeren.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je bouwt actief mee aan een cultuur waarin datageletterdheid en datavaardigheid worden gestimuleerd, en je inspireert collega’s rond het belang en de kracht van een goed uitgebouwde data fabric.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je waakt over de naleving van regelgeving (zoals GDPR), risico’s en auditvereisten binnen de technologische opzet, en werkt daarvoor nauw samen met Data Governance, Security en Cyber Resilience.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Profiel&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Jouw profiel&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je hebt een sterke affiniteit voor dataplatformen, cloudtechnologie en digitale transformatie. Het bezitten van een masterdiploma is een pluspunt.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je hebt minstens enkele jaren relevante ervaring als data architect, cloud data engineer of in een gelijkaardige functie.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je denkt in termen van wat mogelijk is, niet enkel in wat vertrouwd is: je durft bestaande patronen te doorbreken en innovatieve oplossingen te verkennen. Je begrijpt moderne data-architectuurprincipes en hebt een goed inzicht in concepten als een conceptuele data fabric. Je bent vertrouwd met technologieën zoals Azure omgevingen, Terraform, Python, Databricks, DBT, SQL databases, concepten zoals Data catalogs, ELT-tools…&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je hebt ervaring met het opzetten en beheren van data pipelines, CI/CD (X-Ops), (near) real-time integraties, metadata management en begrijpt het belang van geactiveerde metadata binnen een composable architectuur.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Termen als composable, reusable en data-as-a-product zijn voor jou geen buzzwords, maar concrete principes waarmee je dagelijks aan de slag gaat.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je bent een sterke communicator die technische en niet-technische stakeholders verbindt. Je slaagt erin om complexe ideeën helder en overtuigend over te brengen.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je bent leergierig, innovatief en volgt actief de nieuwste trends en ontwikkelingen binnen het data- en cloudlandschap.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je neemt initiatief, denkt oplossingsgericht en weet mensen te enthousiasmeren. Je werkt gestructureerd en met oog voor zowel de strategische doelen als de praktische uitvoering.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je hebt ervaring met projectmatig werken in agile omgevingen. Je weet de balans te bewaren tussen inhoudelijke diepgang en resultaatgerichte uitvoering.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Durf, verbinding focus en eenvoud? Dat zijn waarden waarin jij je helemaal kan vinden&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Aanbod&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ons aanbod&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Je kan rekenen op een gevarieerde job met stimulerende verantwoordelijkheden, plaats voor nieuwe initiatieven en opleidingsmogelijkheden. Verder bieden we jou een marktconform loon aangevuld met een&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.portofantwerpbruges.com/jobs/nl/waarom-werken-bij-havenbedrijf-antwerpen-brugge"&gt;&lt;span&gt;uitgebreid pakket extralegale voordelen&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;&amp;nbsp;met onder meer maaltijdcheques, extralegaal pensioen, hospitalisatieverzekering, mobiliteitsvergoeding en een invaliditeitsverzekering. Onze regelmatige fietsers krijgen een kwalitatieve bedrijfsfiets aangeboden (inclusief fietsonderhoud en pechverhelping).&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Aan de functie cloud data platform architect is de weddeschaal klasse 8 verbonden. Bekijk het overzicht van de &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://media.portofantwerpbruges.com/m/db0af35f42df5c/original/TEKST_Overzicht_Barema_maart_2025.pdf"&gt;&lt;span&gt;loonbarema's per klasse&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Indien de vereiste competenties nog verder ontwikkeld moeten worden, start je in klasse 7 en evolueer je op termijn naar klasse 8.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h2&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Interesse?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Heb je interesse voor deze vacature, bezorg ons dan zo snel mogelijk je CV en motivatiebrief via de knop ‘solliciteer’.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;We sluiten de vacature af zodra we een geschikte kandidaat gevonden hebben. Wij accepteren geen sollicitaties via agencies.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Meer informatie over het selectieproces en &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.portofantwerpbruges.com/over-ons?#waarden"&gt;&lt;span&gt;onze waarden&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; vind je op &lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.portofantwerpbruges.com/jobs/nl/hoe-solliciteren"&gt;&lt;span&gt;onze jobsite&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt;. Bekijk de&amp;nbsp;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;a href="https://media.portofantwerpbruges.com/m/5ea24db8aa2730bc/original/PDF_Competentie_adviseur_NL.pdf"&gt;&lt;span&gt;competentiematrix&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;span&gt; met de vereiste competenties voor deze functie.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;Werken bij Port of Antwerp-Bruges betekent werken in een haven/havenfaciliteit. Hiervoor mag je niet onderworpen zijn aan een havenverbod. Om deze reden zal een uittreksel bedoeld in artikel 596bis van het Wetboek van Strafvordering worden opgevraagd.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Iedereen welkom bij Port of Antwerp-Bruges. We geloven in de kracht van verschil en diversiteit, één met de wereld rondom ons.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;h3&gt;Bedrijf&lt;/h3&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Adres: Zaha Hadidplein&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Vacatures: 5&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Werknemers: 1001-5000&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Sector: Maritime&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>
    <link href="https://editx.eu/en/it-jobs/14750"/>
    <category term="Python"/>
    <category term="Databricks"/>
  </entry>
</feed>
